What's up, guys and girls?
Welcome to my stream.
I will be playing video games for you today.
Actually, that's a lie.
I'll be playing them for myself.
Okay, yeah.
But you get to watch.
And it's gonna be hot and sweaty and hot.
What am I talking about?
I'm a little bit of a weird mood today.
If I seem a little weird today, it's not because I'm weird, okay?
My friend is going through some things and it's been bothering me.
It's been weighing on my mind, I guess.
Worrying about them.
So, I'm gonna distract myself from that by playing video games.
I'm gonna play Animal Well.
You like it when people are sweaty?
I like that, Mr. Ibrahim Dov 5.
Is he in the sky?
In the sky.
And the planets and moons are there.
Yeah, it's gonna be fine.
Hopefully.
We're working on something.
Thank you for being the goat.
Meh.
Oh wait, that's a sheep.
Wait, what does the goat say?
Doesn't the goat say meh?
Maybe.
But thank you for saying that.
Is it still hot in Denmark?
It's not.
It's pretty cold here, yeah.
Same in Denmark.
In fact, it's raining right now.
It's pretty grey outside.
I would say this is a very typical Danish weather experience at the moment.
In fact, my feet are a little cold.
So, I think it's soon time to break out the... the electric socks.
And heat them up.
You finished Outer Wilds two days ago?
Oh, the series.
Okay, okay.
Oh yeah, you gotta play the DLC, Mr. Ibrahim.
The DLC is incredible.
Just have an open mind, is all I'll say, okay?
Hey, Olive Martini, are you burned out from Minecraft?
And do you like onions?
Uh, no and yes.
I wouldn't say I'm burned out from Minecraft.
I still have things to do.
I'm just kind of addicted to Animal Well right now.
I want to play it.
It's like that meme with the guy walking with his girlfriend, and another girl comes walking by, and he looks, you know, back and goes, ooh, that's me with Animal Well right now.
The hell are electric socks?
It's like normal socks, but there's heating elements in them.
And they're incredible, they changed my life.
And they were kind of expensive too.
I spent a thousand kroners on that, which is, I think, 200 dollars, maybe a bit less, 180.
Very pricey pair of socks.
But they have lasted me years, and they have changed my life.
Best investment of my life.
For sure.
Hope you find all the secrets in the game today.
Every single one.
That sounds like a threat.
I will, or maybe that's just me, interpreting it that way.
Yeah, that is expensive.
They are battery pack powered, yeah.
And you charge them, you know, in the outlet.
How much is that in dollars?
180, I think.
I can't do the...
I don't know what the current...
What do you call it?
It's value is.
The fucking transformation.
Wait, how do you wash them?
By hand.
The heating elements can get wet, so it's fine.
You just gotta not put the battery part in there.
So you gotta wash them by hand like the good old days.
It's kind of a pain, but it's...
Trust me, it's worth it.
Yeah, I was charging my socks during the first season of Minecraft.
And in the second one, I started putting them on.
It takes a while.
Poseidon.
What's up, man?
My first time watching you live.
I've been watching the VODs for the past two years, since the first season of Minecraft.
Ooh.
That's a long time.
Good to have you, Poseidon.
Greetings.
I love how blurry the emotes are on the intro screen.
Right?
I made the CRT effect, just like the game.
This old-school retro style.
I thought it looked cool.
Just don't wear socks, walk barefoot in the snow.
Honestly, that's kind of nice.
And then going into a bath afterwards.
I recommend.
Or if you're from Finland, you do that, but with your whole body.
You basically go naked into the snow, and then you jump into the sauna.
I think Isansi would know about that.
I don't know if he's here, but...
It's a normal thing, guys.
Are you a fan of Tron?
I am a fan of Tron.
Yeah.
Especially the soundtrack from the new one.
The soundtrack from the new one is incredible.
But I also like the Ultron.
Just the movie.
Yeah, it's a good one.
Is it snowing in Denmark?
No, it's just raining.
Or drizzling right now.
It's not quite a rain, I would say.
Yeah, the Daft Punk soundtrack is incredible.
Especially the track called The Rizzler.
I think.
I forgot the name.
I swear to you.
But isn't that also a meme nowadays?
Rizz?
Like, having Rizz?
That's not what I mean.
I mean, like, uh...
There's a song called The Rizzler or something.
And it's really good, okay?
Trust me.
Something about Rizz, okay?
Maybe it's Razzler or...
You know...
Revenant or...
Renumination?
Recuperation?
Recklessness?
Maybe?
Walter White?
Willy Wonka?
Wild West?
Okay.
You riffed me up?
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
Daft Well.
Oh, we're playing Daft.
Actually, yeah, it is kind of Tron-like, isn't it?
In a way.
Are the circuits like freeways?
Are you talking about Recognizer?
Yeah, that one!
I think Recognizer.
That may be the one, actually.
Oh my god, I...
Oh, the Rizzler.
Maybe it's that one, then.
Okay, you guys are confusing me.
It's definitely something to do with R and Z, okay?
I finally caught you wailing.
Yes!
What's up, Grey?
Grey the skeleton.
I'm imagining you as the skeleton from, uh...
Oh, what's that game?
You know that game?
With the skeleton making jokes.
Oh my god.
I forgot the name of it.
I'm actually, I'm worried about my memory.
And you will see that today as well if you're following blueprints.
I'm sorry, but...
There may be something wrong with me.
Undertale, that's the one, thank you.
That one.
Uh, Sans!
That was his name.
That's who I'm gonna imagine when I think of your name now.
Have you ever had raw onions?
I had that today!
Onion grill!
I mean, onion girl!
Fitting name.
I made tacos today.
So, um...
This is what I did.
I bought chicken.
And, you know, some spices on it, on the pan.
Chopped it up finely.
Then I had tortillas, of course.
I cut them a little smaller, because I like the small tacos.
And then I had raw onion on that.
Some tomato, some avocado, some lime juice, some chili, some garlic.
Oh my god, it was incredible.
Flour or corn?
Corn tortillas today.
I've been kind of obsessed with making or improving my taco game.
Because I bought some tacos.
They were birria tacos, which I don't know how to make myself.
But chicken close second, I guess.
Or not.
But they were so damn good, I was like, I gotta make this at home.
Because it was way too expensive to keep eating.
It was like a one-time thing.
You're having tortillas today?
Good.
Isanti, I was just talking about you, actually.
Isn't it true you go into the snow, naked, and then you go into the sauna afterward?
I know you do that.
Yeah, see, there you go.
Isanti says yes.
Taco Tuesday, but it's Thursday.
That almost works.
The other way around, maybe?
No, no, no.
You go snow first, then you heat up.
It's actually pretty cool.
No pun intended.
You should play the Oregon Trail.
I know a meme from that game.
You died of dysentery.
Right?
Isn't that from that game?
Maybe I should play it.
I would love to die from dysentery.
In the game, not in real life.
I messed up yesterday.
I used the wrong flour and checked what I could make with this dough, so I made tortillas.
Well, that's good.
Tortillas are nice.
You're gonna have a good time with those.
You can have a good time with those tortillas, okay?
I would love to die.
Hey.
Let's not get all sad in here.
I mean...
It's gonna be fine.
You're going trick-or-treating this year.
We don't really do that in Denmark.
Especially not adults.
33-year-old men walking around trying to get candy.
That sounds like a recipe for calling the police.
I don't know.
Something about that is just...
It's mostly a US thing, I think.
Small kids in Denmark do it, but only in certain cities.
You know?
Dress up as the printer man?
I guess I could.
Would you play Slime Rancher?
Yes, we're playing that today, actually, Onion Girl.
And by today, I mean at some point in the future.
I know about the game, but I don't know what it's about.
But I've heard about it.
And it's on my list, I think.
Dress as Steve from Minecraft?
I think that's how I dress right now.
Hell yeah!
You did hear the last part of my sentence, right?
Just got my PhD application in space physics.
Rejected.
Told me I was top three applicant.
That sucks, man.
I'm sorry to hear that.
But it must be nice to know that you were top three, though.
Keep applying.
You're gonna get it.
For sure.
That sounds great, though.
I mean, not the rejection part, but...
Sounds like you're quite the catch.
You inspired me to play Blueprints.
Good!
I want to start a revolution.
I want more people to play Blueprints.
I've become just like you guys now, hounding everyone else.
Saying, you gotta play Blueprints!
Please play it!
It's so good.
It's such a good game.
It can be a little frustrating sometimes.
There's a bit of RNG in there, but if you can get over that, it's an immaculate game.
It's really cool, and different, and fresh.
I told my dad to play it, so I'm contributing.
That's good.
Good job.
Hope you keep going forever and ever.
I'm not gonna keep going forever and ever.
At some point, I won't have fun anymore, and then I'm gonna stop playing.
But it's kind of cool to know that I'm getting other people to enjoy these things.
Like playing the games.
That's nice.
That's a cool side effect of making videos.
Because when you love something, you just want to share it, right?
Make other people experience it and talk about it.
I haven't started yet, Mr. Tanooki.
We're just talking.
But I'm about to start, actually.
Controller is connected.
Note app is open.
Gun is loaded.
You know, everything.
Uh, drink is on the side.
Memory, deleted, because I don't remember what I did.
I, actually that's not true.
I got X.
Okay.
No USB connection sound.
I, it's because of a loose cable.
Uh, sometimes when I move the controller around, the cable is, like, losing connection, and then it goes buh buh buh buh buh.
It's really, uh, it's really annoying.
But it doesn't happen that often.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Animal well.
What a game so far.
Made by one guy, and the game is only 30 megabytes.
It's, it's kind of blowing my mind.
The guy made the whole engine for the game himself as well.
Which is just, I mean, that's just insanity.
Wow.
Let's go.
Um, I remember quitting here because I wanted to do a bit of a cliffhanger, but I forgot why and how.
What was the cliffhanger?
I was about to do something cool.
Oh, that's right!
Thank God for the markings on the map.
I was gonna, uh, investigate the circled area, because I have been finding notes around the game, giving me arrows, which is a combination for song.
And I suspect it's close by up here, simply because, uh, the other two we found were close by.
Right?
I think, uh, one of them was, let me see, here?
And the other one was here.
So, I mean, the last one's gotta be inside the circle, no?
It's gotta be.
Somewhere here.
Let's go look for it.
Also, did I just...
This is an exit...
Oh, this goes here.
There we go.
Alright.
Now, how do I get up here?
I guess I reversed it, but...
How did that even happen?
You gotta bear with me here.
I gotta remember what I was doing.
Oh, wait!
I'm seeing things.
Check that out over here.
What's that all about?
Something's going on there.
And here!
Interesting.
I see access points.
Uh, how do I make this turn around?
Now that I'm down here, I'm confused.
Save the game.
Just in case.
I mean, it's pretty much saved, but, you know.
I guess there's another way to get up there.
Oh, yeah!
I have new items.
That's right.
Sweet balls.
That felt good.
Holy mother of minus!
We're about to do some puzzling.
Um, why did I want to go up here?
Oh, yeah, I remember.
Oh, I can't get up there.
Okay, okay.
Um, new plan.
Maybe I...
Huh.
How many eggs do I have?
25.
So at 32, we're gonna get something new.
Presumably.
New item, perhaps, or a new path.
Something like that.
This area is the bullshit place.
Absolutely impossible over here.
Not sure, uh, what to do about that.
Maybe we'll try again today.
But I do think we need an item there.
I don't think it's a skill issue, because I have quite a big amount of skill.
So that shouldn't be the issue.
Uh, let me make this guy turn around.
Oh, that's the other side.
This way, please.
Okay, here we go.
Look at that sweetness.
Here.
Go.
Oh my god.
Uh, why am I doing this?
Right.
Okay, we gotta investigate this area now for clues on the wall.
This will make it more apparent when we see it.
Go.
Oh, what?
What do you mean I was safe?
I guess I wasn't.
Fuck, that scared me.
Holy shit.
Oh god.
No!
Okay, we're fine.
Fuck, that scared me.
That's a frisbee.
That's a bubble.
That's the one I needed.
Up again.
Good.
Man, this game kind of makes me want to play some of the really old games.
That are like 2D.
Oh, shh!
What am I doing?
I was thinking of other things.
That's what I was doing.
I already hate my gameplay.
I hate it.
It'll be fine though.
I'm a routine gamer.
I don't just give up like that.
Hup!
Oh, shh!
I missed it.
Okay, we can still make it.
Wait, we can't!
We can, we can.
Wait, go.
Hiya wah wah.
That was way too close.
Okay.
Are we seeing anything in this area?
Not seeing much.
Boy, that was close.
Okay, good.
Let's put on this.
So there's a little path down here.
Okay, so this was the first arrow we found.
The other arrow was pretty much right beneath me, right?
I wish I could zoom in a little more on this map.
I don't care if the pixels become, you know, or fill the entire screen.
I'm fine with that.
So it's right below me.
I see a little area, like, up here.
On the map.
Right above me here, to the right, there's something.
At least according to the map.
Oh!
What?
How did that happen?
Okay.
It's kind of annoying that this is facing this way every time.
I may have to change that.
Also, let's just check this area.
So that's the one that takes me down to the bottom part.
Right.
I'm trying to look for, um...
arrows.
There's an arrow up here.
Let me go look at that again.
Oh!
Spikes!
Forgot about those.
Damn it.
This is not easy to do, man.
This little mechanic here is, uh...
It's kind of easy, but it's also hard.
If that's...
If that makes sense.
I can't believe I did it again.
For fuck's sake.
No more messing up.
We're just gonna go up there now.
And we're gonna save the game with the thing reversed.
So I don't have to do this every time.
That's the plan.
Fuck!
Like that.
And then we go down and save the game.
This is the configuration that I like.
What a configuration!
Holy shit!
You've never seen anything like this.
And maybe we look here.
Actually, I see something over here.
Slight differences in color, like right below me.
It looks a little bit interesting, doesn't it?
Is that just me?
Wait.
Okay.
I was checking whether or not that could enter.
It couldn't.
Man, the frisbee is actually a great way to check.
If you can enter somewhere.
There we go.
Easy.
I mean, look how...
Look how hard that is to see.
The arrows there.
You see them?
And right now, I'm straight...
Or right below the other arrows.
So they could form a triangle, maybe, with...
Arrows over here?
Okay.
I am not sure where those arrows are.
They ought to be close.
Checking out the background texture.
Okay, well, I think we've checked this area enough.
We can go somewhere else.
Although, I do have a feeling that...
Maybe in here, there's something going on.
Ah, we should try and focus on this over here, I think.
That could be interesting.
So I see a potential way down by...
Oh, now I reversed it.
But you know what?
Having it this way first is actually better, because I can easily go up and reverse it.
So this is the better start configuration, for sure.
Maybe the last clue is down there with the...
With the dogs.
So here...
I'm not seeing anything.
And that one's gonna take me back up to there.
Maybe it's all the way up here.
Somewhere.
Or maybe even in this room.
Maybe up here in this room.
I mean, I would assume here, right?
On the other side.
And that means we have to go through here.
But I think I checked that already.
And maybe there was a chest there.
I don't recall.
I wanna say there was a chest there.
Oh, boy, that was close.
Bubble time.
Take me.
So now that I'm back...
Maybe I should just try going a new direction, actually.
Yeah.
I'll look for this later.
So this one was interesting.
We ascended this right here.
And we appeared on the bottom.
So it looks like the map is some kind of cyclic.
I guess in the vertical direction, at least.
Unless it's like a secret path.
It was kinda difficult to get up there, right?
I had to do a lot of jumping through hoops.
Now, where are the flames at?
There's one flame here.
And that looks like it can be accessed via this.
So surely that should work.
And to get up there...
I guess going to the egg room makes sense.
So the bear...
Yeah, let's go back.
Let's see if I remember this.
Oh, love that.
Okay.
But which bear is it?
Is it this bear or the other bear?
It was not this one.
Let me write that on the map.
Bear.
Let's call it bear 2.
Bear 2.
Do I want to be here?
I guess so.
It's not a bad spot.
Let's go left.
Oh, not that way.
Left.
Really trying to look for...
secret paths here.
I need that.
What?
Oh, I hit the mist.
I can't do that.
I can't hit the mist.
That one I did.
I guess we go up here.
I do have memories of this.
Yeah, we can't progress here.
Oh, nice.
We gotta get to that elevator again, I guess.
Ah, but wait.
In order to get to here, we need to appear from here.
Because the thing only goes down.
Unless we can find a way to reverse the operation of this elevator.
Where could that be?
Also, what is this drawing I made right here?
What's going on with that?
The flame is right there, man.
Can't be that hard to get.
Let's go this way.
Hey, birdies.
If I climb up here...
Yeah, there's no way to make it there in time.
Or is there?
Maybe it's a skill issue.
There's not, though.
There's no time at all.
There's no way.
Yeah, you can't do it.
It almost feels like there's time, right?
But there's just not really time.
Can I somehow ascend faster?
What happens if I do this?
Oh, it falls down.
Okay.
Yeah, I don't think I can get up there.
Not right now, at least.
Also, hey birdie, do you like frisbees?
Oh, oh!
Hurry!
I'm sorry!
Oh my god!
Leave me!
Okay.
He doesn't like frisbees.
We know that now?
That was actually horrific.
How- what a gruesome death that was.
Wow.
Um.
Let me go through the other bear.
Bear one.
Now I'm here.
Let me call that bear one.
If I go this- I can't go that way.
Yes, I can, because we can move Brian.
Why- what is- what is this?
Oh, an arrow pointing to here.
Let's go check out that arrow I made.
Surely that will be fruitful.
Wait, I can't go this way.
Never mind, I can't go that way.
I was misinformed by my own vision.
We can check out the egg room, I guess.
Maybe there's a consolation prize for not having quite enough eggs?
No?
Notice also the pattern on that peacock.
On the feathers.
Maybe it means something.
Probably not.
But, you know, you gotta question everything here.
It feels like, um, there's just secrets everywhere, you know?
Yeah, let me try and get up here again.
We have a bunch of arrows that we drew.
Surely we'll find something.
This way.
Ah, actually.
Do I go that way?
Let me investigate my drawing up here.
I do remember this spot, but I don't remember this, uh, rodent sitting here, huh?
Was this just, okay, it was a chest.
So that one's done.
Oops.
Let's remove it.
Fixed.
There's no more chests here.
Good to get it out of the way, though.
Mentally, I mean.
Okay.
Now I want to go up.
We're gonna investigate all these arrows.
I also want to find more, uh, shark connections.
Okay, we got evil birds.
Right above me.
There's a flame.
And I'm gonna save my game over here.
Yes.
And we have this, uh, dog penguin.
So weird.
Maybe they're doing experiments with merging animals, you know?
Uh, okay, so there was this part here.
I think I tried doing this, but I couldn't for some reason.
Oh yeah, you can't just jump through that.
Yeah, okay.
And you can't go up like this, right?
No.
Okay.
Yeah, we gotta hit that button up there.
Whoops!
Let me do that.
Let me put a marker here.
For...
What should the marker for button be?
Maybe a spiral.
That's kind of like a button, right?
Does it never end?
Okay, I made an arrow up there for some reason.
Let's check it out.
Oh yeah, this spot.
This was a bit of an interesting one.
Let me try this again.
Uh, how did that work?
So we go here.
Throw that one.
That's right.
Let's see if we can't get up there where I put a marker.
Good thing you can't just appear in the middle of a wall, right?
That would be gruesome death.
Oh, can I even get through there?
I gotta go here.
Do I remember...
I don't remember this.
I do remember the dogs, but how about this up here?
How would I do that?
It's probably accessible...
somehow.
I'm sorry, doggo.
I was gonna give you the frisbee.
Oh, dude, hello?
Grab the...
Okay, okay, good, good, good.
I mean, you know what?
I could also just say, uh...
What's going on, my dude?
You can't get to me.
Hehehehe.
Too bad, doggos!
You don't have the required strength!
Aha!
The master of bubbles, it's I!
See you later.
No fetch today.
So why is there a question mark over my character?
Oh, maybe because I'm standing in front of the door, I see.
We can definitely go up here, I think.
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, we can definitely do something here.
No!
I'm not a frisbee!
Oh god, I'm gonna die.
Shit.
Oh god.
Okay, you know what?
Maybe that's not a good idea.
Catch.
Wait.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What am I doing here, actually?
Oh, right, okay, I see.
Catch!
Oh god, oh god.
Oh, he's just gonna keep chasing it!
Even if I'm down here?
Don't eat me!
Oh, it works!
He's perpetually chasing it!
That's a huge discovery!
Very good, very good.
Oh yeah, eat that.
Oh, that's so neat.
Oh, we got a thingy!
Oh, it's bear three?
Wait, what?
Okay.
I don't know where the hell you're gonna lead.
Why are there so many bears?
Yeah, this is bear three!
Okay.
Sure.
Open the map.
Bear three.
And we should also mark this down here.
Bear one.
You know what?
We should just call it B1.
That's horrible.
B2.
This is B3.
And this is Fush.
I don't remember why I called it that.
Sounds like fish.
Okay, well, we're slowly unlocking all of these.
No!
That was a mistake.
A horrible mistake.
Oh god.
Here, chase.
Chase it, brother!
You know you like it.
Check for secrets on the way up.
I have a feeling.
Fuuuuck!
You cannot be real!
I'm actually so bad at this game.
Like, platforming is...
I will never be good at that.
I swear to you.
Fucking hell.
Don't fall in the fucking hole!
Oh!
That's another way of doing it, I guess.
That's brilliant, but I like this.
Have I been here?
I guess I have, since the map is here.
I just don't remember this at all.
Thank you.
Now, something's going on in the center here.
Let's try to throw one of these.
Okay.
Just because the game was giving me one here, I thought maybe I needed this.
Eat that fruit.
Okay, here we definitely have some stuff here.
Is it slinky time?
I see.
And this one is gonna...
Okay.
Right.
And there's a chest there.
I see.
Wait.
What was the plan here?
Yeah, the plan was to do that exactly.
That was actually right.
Oh, that's not enough.
Ah, too slow.
I think this can be done.
Okay.
Well, in that case...
Maybe I...
Yeah.
Okay, I see, I see, I see.
Take me up here.
What's that gonna do?
It was already open, wasn't it?
I see.
We got more whales.
Yeah, let's work on this then.
Oh, that's interesting.
Periodic.
Okay.
Hmm.
And this one?
Aha.
Okay.
Periodic.
That is weird.
Why would I like to do this?
Can't I just walk?
Oh.
Oh, I didn't see that little, uh...
Narrow hole there.
I see.
We need to frisbee this.
Okay.
The question is, how do we time this?
Oh god.
This one?
So, one, two, three.
One, two, three.
Okay.
So, what is this doing?
Oops.
One, two, three.
Turns it on and off.
Gets it up there.
Maybe that's the first step.
Get it up there.
And now she's gonna do that.
Okay.
Wait, what?
I'm not sure how that worked.
Why?
What?
I'm not understanding.
But I did it.
Reference egg.
Oh.
Nice.
Good to have a test sample.
Control.
A control.
Always needed.
Now.
Let's try and figure this one out.
I was thinking.
If I throw it from up there.
Why stand here?
There's not.
It's not gonna.
No.
Quick.
Okay.
Man.
Wait.
How is this gonna be done?
How else can I put something in there delayed?
I was thinking.
Maybe if we raise this box over here.
And then throw this slinky from up there.
But.
Is that gonna work?
Wait.
I can't even.
Oh yeah.
Right.
Of course.
Do this.
Oh.
We made it.
Nice.
A brown egg.
I've seen those in real life.
They exist.
They're real.
It's kind of creepy.
But they exist.
I know.
Crazy stuff.
Now.
It feels like there's more over here.
Like.
Oh.
That's just the button icon.
Okay.
Now.
This can't be it up here though.
Right?
Let me.
I wish I could stand on the lamps and swing on them.
That would be the best thing ever.
Now.
I see a path that I can take.
So.
I didn't manage to get the item in time.
Chase it.
Oh my god.
Come on.
Chase the goddamn thing.
Before I lose my damn mind.
Run!
Can we make it?
We made it.
Wow.
Okay.
So, I still have... whoa.
No, not yet.
Eat, then save.
Call them up.
That's a spearfish!
On a pillar.
And there's lots of empty pillars.
Hmm.
I mean, I know how to traverse this.
It's gonna take a while, but you know.
I'm in it for the long haul.
They're facing different directions.
This means something.
Ah!
Okay.
Fuck me.
He's in the water.
We gotta stay high.
Ah!
Unbelievable.
Stay high.
And stay hydrated.
Don't forget to hydrate people.
Fuck me!
I'm so bad at this game.
Wait, what am I doing, bro?
Hello?
Just do that!
Surely you won't catch me, right?
Okay.
Well, there it is.
It's the forbidden egg.
Now I really wanna eat it.
Put it in my mouth.
Make my tummy go round.
Wait.
How do we move this box?
Now I'm intrigued.
Is that gonna come back?
Nope.
Hmm.
We need a square somewhere.
Let me go back.
Oh!
Wait, what?
I can... I can almost walk on the water!
Look at this!
Isn't that interesting?
Wait.
There's something here.
Look at these stairs.
Oh!
Cuckoo!
Ah!
Haha!
I'm a genius!
Holy shit!
Wow!
Okay.
Time to blow shit up, people!
Oh my god.
It's bear mama and bear kid.
Bear four.
Oh, you're throwing rocks?
Wait.
Wait a minute.
I was about to say I've been here!
Hmm.
But I haven't been here.
Wait a minute.
Why is this like...
Oh, right.
Because of that.
Hold on.
I'm not done here.
Oh!
I can't go back!
Slink.
Okay.
Rip.
I was gonna investigate the other side with the slinky, but...
Okay.
Sure.
Also, I really should be examining every screen I enter for these arrows.
Why does it look like the background is giving me the middle finger right now?
If you see it, you see it.
I see it.
Down.
Jump, jump, jump.
Okay.
Oh.
Alright.
What is that sound?
I don't like the sound of that.
Oh, it's getting green.
Oh, it's from that puzzle in there.
Wait, wait a minute.
It is cyclic on the horizontal as well.
Okay.
Interesting.
This is a slinky.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, you gotta be faster.
You gotta be way fast.
In fact...
Check this out.
That should work.
Okay.
So, we have...
Slinky...
Eight, one, two, three.
Oh, my God.
I missed it.
Maybe I can just...
Okay, hold on.
Slinky, one, two.
Slinky, one, two?
Oh, shit.
That was only one.
One, two.
Ah!
Okay, that's very difficult.
I think I'm onto the right thing here with the...
With the disc.
So, one, two, three.
One, two, three.
I missed it.
Oh, I'm way too late.
Okay.
So, we go...
Oh, wait.
It doesn't come back like that.
Okay.
Bro, this is...
This is...
Difficult.
Ah!
Oh, wait.
I didn't throw this slinky.
Eugh!
Wait, maybe I...
No, that doesn't work.
Maybe... Oh, it's a...
Oh!
Go!
No!
Oh, shit!
I think you gotta...
R-ride through that with the...
With the slinky-doo.
Unless...
Can I do things on...
On the bubble?
Okay.
I can do things on the bubble.
Double trouble.
Whoops.
Ah!
Jesus Christ.
Okay, you know what?
I have a better idea.
I found the perfect height.
Here.
This is it.
Oh,
bitch!
Yeah!
Bitch!
There we go!
Look at that!
Plantic!
That looks like a...
Zucchini!
Actually.
I know my fruits.
And I think I do.
Oh, shit.
Can I go through here?
Yep!
It worked.
Force it in your stomach.
Okay, that's...
Okay, nice.
Nice.
We got it.
But can I not...
Uh...
Is there an easier way out of here?
This can't be it, right?
Like, I have to go all the way back?
That feels wrong.
My senses are tingling.
Can I connect to the room on my right?
Somehow.
Let me do this again.
First try, watch.
Actually, I can just stand here.
Like, it...
There's no way it's just...
Oh, I guess it's just a way back, I guess.
That makes sense.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well...
Moving on.
Now, you're gonna throw that crab at me.
That's fine.
I don't mind.
This spot.
So, I feel like there's something about this, right here.
With these bears.
Like, would you like some discs in your life?
You know what?
I'm gonna go fuck you up now.
That's right.
You made me mad.
Can't be throwing rocks like that.
Oh, I thought I could stand up there.
I can.
Okay.
Also, one, two, three.
One, two, three.
Let me scare you.
You're not scared by that?
What if I hit you in your face?
Boik!
No, you don't like...
You like music?
Come on, you like that song.
No?
Wait, I wanna get back up here.
I mean...
There's definitely something here.
I mean, look at how all things connect in here.
I guess I have to go back here.
And how do I do that?
I use bear number...
Oops.
One.
Bear one.
Okay, let's do it.
I also keep forgetting I have this, uh...
Fast travel method.
Nice.
I kind of expected to use different melodies to travel different places.
That was my initial thought.
But I guess that's not the case.
Uh... B1.
Here we are.
So from B1, we're gonna go...
Up.
And down and left and...
I hope that connects.
Actually, I see a way that connects really beautifully.
I think.
We gotta go up.
From... here actually.
But how do I get above?
The right side?
I think through the egg room.
Yeah.
All right, Brian.
Wake up!
Call on your people.
Wait a sec.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This place.
Wait.
Oh!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
No?
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Uh...
Take a picture.
I have no clue.
There we go.
Uh... put it in here.
Just gonna put it like there, I guess.
Copy this.
There's, uh...
Some kind of melody going on here.
We can probably extend that.
Just like that.
Beautiful.
Okay.
Well, I don't know.
Maybe the opposite order.
Wait, did I count right?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, six, five, four, three, two...
Yeah, I did.
Uh, let me try the other order.
Maybe it's backwards.
Maybe I have to seduce these guys with it.
Maybe I stand on them and do it.
So, one, two, three, four...
Remember we also had the, um...
The smileys there.
You see it in the bottom?
The smileys.
Like...
What's all this about, right?
This has to be related to the music as well somehow.
I'm imagining.
Could be wrong.
Where else have I seen these, uh, dice?
Oh, look at the lamp!
I broke the game.
This once so polished game has been taken to its knees.
I made it happen.
Up here.
So, the plan now was to get up here.
To figure out what's going on there.
I'm honestly just looking for a new path to go.
I don't really know where to go.
Like, I'm kinda lost in this game right now.
Just go left.
Oh, you.
Um...
Grab it!
What's going on here?
I'm still looking for arrows.
But I'm honestly probably way too far away from that.
Like, it wouldn't make sense to put that in the same area.
Like I mentioned.
Okay.
This is not the way.
I gotta go up to the path above me.
Alright, let's save again.
Wait, I can eat this.
There we go.
Man.
The dog sounds so thirsty.
I wanna give it a bowl of water.
Can I do that?
Look at these dog statues.
This is dog kingdom.
Where's the candles at?
What?
I can't...
Aw, man!
What?
Okay.
Fuck.
Guess we can't go that way.
Um...
Well, shit!
Where do I go?
I guess I go manually?
Uh...
It's really hard to traverse this map.
Like, it's so convoluted.
What is that, anyway?
It's a big pile of nothing.
Now I wanna go up here.
And then I guess I go down where the dog was.
This way?
Okay, you're not the type that follows me, that's good.
Too dark, great.
Wait, that looks interesting.
Can I get up there?
I do remember this spot.
Don't wanna go that way.
Wait, wasn't something evil here?
Maybe not.
Okay, we're getting closer.
I also put a question mark here for some reason?
Why did I do that?
B?
Did I write B?
B for what?
Remove that.
I don't know what I was thinking.
But whatever had to be done here, I did already.
I did put light on that, so we're good.
Doesn't that look like a path?
Oh!
It is!
Oh.
That's it?
Aw, man!
Okay.
Oi!
Ooh!
Now we're talking.
Wait, what was my problem last time here?
Why did I...
think I couldn't go this way?
I made an arrow here.
What?
Okay.
I don't know, but this is a shortcut now.
Let me just see what was down here.
Oh, the Bubble Kingdom.
Actually, we have outstanding things in the Bubble Kingdom.
Look at all these outstanding things.
Question marks everywhere.
But let's take that later.
I want to continue my current quest.
Which is...
Not that way.
This way.
Okay.
Lever.
No evil creatures of the night.
That's good.
Uh...
We gotta pull that lever.
Okay.
Right.
Okay, we're almost there.
We're almost there.
Uh...
I guess I'll just throw a Frisbee to you.
There you go.
Good catch.
Here we go.
I remember this spot.
Question this.
Yeah, I'm just gonna go up like this.
Oh yeah.
This room.
That was pretty much a dead end, no?
Yeah, I'm not seeing anything...
Peculiar about this.
Except the skull.
The skull is a little, uh...
Scary.
Now, I see a way up.
Crabcakes.
I should be more patient.
Oh my god.
It's hard to do when you can't see anything.
You know, when you transition from screen to screen.
It's really tough.
Just gonna put that there just in case I fall down again.
God.
Damn it.
I'm actually close.
I guess I already had it.
Oh no, it's...
Okay.
So we have to do this.
Crab.
Ah.
God, verdammt.
As they say in the Netherlands, I think.
I'm actually not sure what they say in the Netherlands.
No!
Fuck!
Goddamn Dutch people!
I didn't mean anything by that.
The Netherlands were distracting me with their dams and all that right now.
All the water manipulation was on my...
I've been up here!
Bruh.
Alright.
Well, why can't I go up there?
How do I get to this fucking point?
I'm so confused.
Where do I go to?
I guess I go up here somehow, but how do I get up there?
Bear 3.
Let's go back again.
Holy shit!
Bear 3 is located where?
Top left.
Okay.
So what?
We go down now, or what?
Oh, this thing is...
Oh, no.
We're back here now.
Yo!
Fuck me.
This is the hardest game I've ever played.
Uh...
We gotta go right.
Let me go down.
And then left.
I remember this...
Place.
I was using this.
But I can also just...
Yo-yo.
Oh my god.
That's too risky.
Break it.
There's also a little spot there.
You see that?
Oh, I didn't mean to.
Okay.
Guess we're taking a trip.
Let me also break this.
Oh my gosh.
You're fucking kidding me.
You're fucking kidding me!
Oh...
Where was I, man?
That kills me?
Oh my... I don't know where I am.
Let's go back again.
Bear 3.
Up we go.
And then...
Back we go.
Here, down.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Let's do this again.
In fact, while I wait for that...
Uh...
Not quite.
Did the thing just break on me?
Break it off.
There we go.
Finally.
Alright.
Let me grab this.
There we go.
Okay.
For my next trick...
I'm gonna do nothing up here.
Currently.
Okay.
I thought something was there.
Break that.
Strong yo-yo.
I remember this...
Somewhat.
There's a path to fall down here.
Isn't that kinda interesting?
Yeah.
How would I get up there?
Oh, it's probably the way...
Back down after all this?
Wait.
I haven't been here.
What the heck?
Uh...
Okay.
What's this?
Aha!
Good boy.
Uh...
Now you need to go the other way, please.
Are you gonna follow this?
You're not?
Okay.
Hmm.
Let me do...
This first.
Lovely.
Come here.
Good.
Sir!
Are you not attracted by my yo-yo anymore?
Come here.
How do I make you attracted to my yo-yo?
Hmm.
Maybe go above again?
Come here.
Yeah!
That's it.
Beautiful.
Okay.
Brine is always a little, uh, difficult to handle.
I found a key!
Ooh!
Now the question is...
Which door is it gonna work on?
I put a question mark...
Why did I put a question mark here?
Remove it.
What?
Yeah, I don't like that.
No question marks allowed.
Whoa.
What?
Wait, where am I?
Oh!
That's a candle!
That's a bat!
Yo!
Oh!
Bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup-bup.
No thanks.
Oh jeez!
Okay, I don't know what to do.
Are you- are you hurt by this?
Are you hurt?
Okay.
Hey.
I guess I gotta go up to the left?
Let me try some firecrackers.
I don't have any!
Hey!
Catch!
Oh god.
Yo!
Crap!
I'm almost dead.
Okay, so this is the path down again.
I see.
Oh man.
Uh...
Emergency exit strategy engage.
This is how we're gonna do it.
Do your thing.
Oh shit, I may be too late.
Oh shit!
Gooooo!
Holy shit!
We made it.
Okay.
Uh...
What now?
We got a giant kangaroo.
There we go.
Is that another recess?
Place ca- Oh!
Oh!
I see!
So that's what we need.
Uh-huh.
That's what those are for.
I have one key, one match, 29 eggs.
I mean, obviously there's something there.
So how do we enter?
Ah!
Egg as a service?
What does that even mean?
I want a DLC egg.
That's what I want.
Uh...
I don't wanna go in there.
I guess we can remove this stuff now.
That's gone, this is gone.
Uh...
What am I supposed to do here?
I guess nothing.
How do we open that over there?
Fuck, I don't...
Uh...
I'm trying to look at the screen.
I guess I can hide in certain places, right?
Oh, shit!
Like, if I go here...
Actually, I die...
If I get hit, I die.
I die.
This is very dangerous.
Can I...
Go some...
Somewhere else?
Oh!
I have this now.
Let's try that.
That's right!
Get fucked!
One more!
Oh!
What'd I do?
I just did something.
What'd I just do?
Oh god, I don't wanna use my last one.
Uh...
Maybe I soothe you?
No, you hate it, you hate it.
Okay.
Uh...
Down.
Uh, you know what?
I know what's gonna happen.
This path over here...
That path, it's gonna open when we put all the, uh...
Fragments in this thing.
When it becomes a full circle.
Then things will take place.
Uh, the question is, where do we go now?
Oops.
Uh, let me have a look around.
What is an obvious path?
There's also recess here!
That's...
Weird, isn't it?
Uh...
There's this...
Uh, button here.
We don't know how to get to.
There's also this part over here, but...
That's gonna lead us down here.
We did that already.
Actually, there's here.
That looks like something, doesn't it?
Looks like there's something missing here.
There's also an arrow here.
Oh, that one I didn't know how to...
Deal with, I guess.
Why did I mark that?
I don't know where to go.
I feel like I completed the whole map.
Well, obviously not, but...
I don't see a path.
Where am I...
Where am I supposed to go?
I mean, this right here is interesting, right?
I feel like we should go to bubble country.
Because I have so many question marks there.
I forgot exactly why I couldn't solve whatever was going on there at the time, but...
Maybe I can now.
And I'm here now.
Fair three.
Man, the flame is right there.
Also this right here.
But I'm pretty sure I investigated most of this...
Upwards motion.
Last time.
I could go try do this again, but...
It seems impossible.
It's almost like I need some kind of, uh...
Sprint sneakers, you know, to run faster or something.
This also looks like maybe a path down.
Doesn't it?
Let's poke, uh, let's make a, uh...
Little arrow there.
Here.
Now there's this place, of course, down here, but I can't progress there.
Because there's a stupid bird.
But I'm not sure if I tried the, um...
The...
Firecrackers.
On him yet.
That could be an idea.
And then there's also, uh, the big cat.
The creature.
That's chasing me all over.
Like, obviously I gotta bring that, um...
Thing somewhere at some point.
Bear two is here.
I don't know where to go!
I feel like...
I don't know what to do.
There's this spot over here on the right, but I don't know how to get there.
Why did I put a skull there?
Why is there a skull there?
Question mark as well.
Maybe we should investigate this again.
Uh, but isn't this just...
I don't want to go back to this area.
This area is my nightmare.
There's a heart here?
I don't know why.
Yeah.
So how do we get to bubble region?
Uh...
The best path, I guess...
I don't know.
I mean, we can go to the...
What do you call it?
The hub area, but we can't go up from there.
I guess from the egg room and then take a massive path, or what?
Bear one?
Bear one.
Okay.
Bear one is up here.
Wait a minute.
Did I open all the mouths?
Uh, fish?
Hello?
Wait a sec.
I forgot...
to put that in here.
F1.
Formula one.
Um...
And that was, of course...
F1.
This is F2.
There we go.
All right!
Now we can also investigate this, uh...
weird marker that I put.
Oh, I put that for animal, because I love animals.
That's right.
I love animals.
Let's not forget that.
So this is where all the candles are, but I guess I have to go all the way around them.
Let me try the other, uh, fish.
I had F1 and F2.
There we go!
Okay, that's much better.
I like that.
F2 is here.
Actually, getting these markers on the map is really important right now.
Okay, good.
Let's go investigate these mysteries.
What else do I see on the map?
I go in the drink.
Because I want to go that way, or...
No, I want to go left, actually.
This way.
Oh, but I can't.
It's closed now.
I need that, though.
But if I go up...
That's not gonna bring me down here.
And this shark is going the other way, unfortunately.
I guess I gotta take the long path.
Yeah.
Grab that.
That one is really hard to go up.
Like, you really have to be precise here.
In fact, is that even possible?
How the hell did I get up there last time?
I can't.
I have to go some other path.
The worst part about this is, I'm going to a place where I'm not even sure I can do anything.
You know?
And it's taking me FOREVER to get there.
Like, I don't know.
I don't know what to do, man.
I guess I'll go up here instead.
Um...
Here?
Maybe?
Oh my god.
How the fuck are you supposed to do this game without the bee wand?
Oh, fuck!
What am I doing?
I'm getting so impatient now.
Like, it feels like every area needs it now.
Okay.
So from here, maybe I can go around.
Eat that.
Descend.
Go.
Save the game!
Please.
Thank you.
Okay.
Now, I see a little something here, perhaps.
Let's quickly investigate.
While we're here.
Uh...
I think the only way up is over here.
Aha!
A dazzle egg!
Good.
I am bedazzled.
That's wonderful.
Am I seeing anything else?
Hidden, hidden, hidden...
things.
Alright, let's move on then.
That was a nice little extra.
Now I want to go down here.
That was the plan.
Now I'm up here.
That was a long path just to get up here.
I'm also gonna destroy this, because I know I'm gonna fuck it up.
So, is this the path I wanna go?
Let's see.
If I do that, then I'm gonna be able to go down on the right, it seems.
And then I go further down...
That looks... doable, actually.
That looks like a thing I can do.
Gotta be super careful, though.
A death here would be very undesirable.
Hold on.
Secrets...
More secrets up here, maybe.
Ah, it's so tough to hit it!
There we go.
No, I don't think there's anything up there.
But, I do wanna destroy the entire floor.
I think I already did this once, but...
Alright.
Oh!
Fuck!
That scared me, man.
Alright.
Nothing there, huh?
Then we go down.
I'm being very thorough here.
Now, wasn't this the place where there was an evil creature of the night?
Who wanted a piece of me.
Wait, I thought I could go to the right here!
No!
Well, fuck, what do I do then?
Bro.
Okay.
I can't go that way, cause this door's blocked.
So I wanna go down here, right?
But I can't.
Unfortunately.
Uh...
I just wanna get to this damn region.
I can't decipher this map.
Do we have to go all the way around here somehow?
And...
How the hell did I get down here?
There's gotta be a way.
Oh shit, yeah.
That's not a problem, actually.
I don't know why I'm going here.
This is not gonna help me.
Yeah, I can't go that way.
Oh my god.
Okay.
I have no clue how to get down there.
I have no clue!
It's insane.
It's actually just insane.
How the hell did I get down there?
I gotta come from here...
I mean, I went this way, right?
I went this way, but I can't go in there anymore.
Can I somehow deactivate that door?
Maybe I missed that.
Let's go back.
Okay.
Um...
Yeah, go up here, I guess.
We just take this way.
Yeah.
Then we go down here.
Yeah, so the door is here, but...
Oh, wait!
Leave her.
Holy fucking shit, I forgot about that one.
Look how tiny it is.
Okay.
Whoops.
Didn't mean to do that.
Slowly descend.
We have to go through a whole gauntlet just to get back down here.
Right.
I do remember this.
Okay.
Nice.
Save the damn game!
Thank God.
Okay.
We can go down now.
And this is just to get here!
I don't even know if there's anything here, you know?
Right, we did that one.
Looks like we're done in this part for sure.
Okay, so...
Okay, yeah.
You are gonna be angry.
That's fine.
Yep, look at that.
Shit!
There we go!
What do we have here?
Looks like something needs to go in here.
You see that?
It's like a little slot for something.
Weird.
Whoops.
What'd I just do?
Oh, no, no.
There we go.
I think I'm gonna write...
What should I write?
Some...
Let's make an arrow.
Something...
Goes...
In...
Slot.
Excuse my handwriting.
I'm writing with a mouse.
It's very difficult.
You're right.
Okay, so...
We know something's going on there.
We just gotta bring some kind of thing over there, I think.
This is definitely...
Let me actually...
Before I...
Think too fast.
Could I somehow...
I didn't even try this yet.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll be back for that.
Right, we gotta go all the way to the left now.
Oh, you asshole!
Absolutely incredible.
Wow!
Okay, you know what?
Go eat...
Something.
I'm outta here.
There we go.
Much easier.
Eat that.
Don't hit the spike!
I told you not to hit the spike.
And what did you do?
You hit the spike.
Look for secrets in here now.
Yeah!
Down there!
What was the deal here?
Oh, I remember...
I remember this part.
Oh...
Okay.
Hold on.
Can I stand on my...
Slinky dink?
No!
Okay.
Hmm...
I didn't jump off.
I'm back here!
Oh, fuck off, man!
Oh!
Dude, this game is fucking hard!
Are you shitting me?
Wow.
Just wow.
Ah!
Go on a disc!
We have three HP now.
And go.
Okay.
What else?
Can I do anything else in here?
Fucking vines are in the way.
That doesn't do anything.
Can I stand on the chest?
Somehow.
Fuck, I don't understand.
There's something here.
What?
How am I here?
Okay, I'm not sure what's going on.
See ya!
Oh!
Fuck!
Okay.
Okay, so there was something up there on the right.
I do remember that.
Aw, shit.
Good thing you don't lose HP from going in the water, man.
That would have been...
A disaster.
Oh wait, I can just jump.
Wait, what?
There's no way there's nothing.
I don't believe that.
You can't be real.
Really?
Um...
Okay.
Well, I guess Bubble Kingdom didn't do anything for us.
You know what?
I'm gonna scrap Bubble Kingdom.
No, I'm gonna go give that thing another try over here.
Since I'm here.
It takes forever.
Like, it's quite the journey to get to Bubble Kingdom.
Okay.
Nooooo!
Never mind.
I guess we're coming back to Bubble Kingdom.
Okay.
Uh, how many eggs do I have?
31!
Okay, okay, we're close.
To something.
To greatness, I like to imagine.
Uh, let's save the game here.
Yep.
And then?
We're gonna go...
You know what?
Let's go find the frickin' arrows.
Here's what we're gonna do, okay?
This is the most systematic exploration of a game you're gonna ever see.
Also, what is it with you, quacky?
Something's going on with that duck, guys.
I'm telling you.
Also, this cat.
Something's going on with that.
Did it change?
It's the same.
Yeah.
Nothing changed.
This spot.
Basically, here's the plan.
I'm gonna go through every screen there is.
Over here.
And we're gonna look for arrows.
Okay?
So, this is the first screen.
I'll...
Oops.
I didn't think you'd come all the way over here.
I am not seeing any arrows.
But I could be wrong.
Of course.
But I don't think there are arrows here.
Up!
Made it.
This place looks like an arrow place, doesn't it?
I would totally put an arrow here.
Or five.
Maybe in the water?
Slinky in the water trick.
Never gets old.
Okay.
Fine.
What was this deal?
Oh, that was a button, right?
That was a button here.
I remember.
Alright, so we checked these screens.
Nothing.
Next.
This is the next screen.
Let's keep an eye out.
If I see the arrows, I will let you know by doing a...
a tiny scream.
It'll be a tiny yell.
Okay, I'm not seeing any arrows on this screen.
As you can tell by the lack of yelling.
So we're gonna go down to the right now.
Are you kidding me?
You know what?
I've had it.
I'm bubbling my way down.
I'm terrible at this game.
I'm so bad.
Show me your secrets, cat!
Meow!
Bubbles.
Okay.
We try this again.
No more messing up now.
Slow and, uh, calculated here.
How the hell did I do this last time?
It's impossible to get down there!
I can't...
Take it.
I don't understand.
How that's supposed to be done.
I feel like that guy playing Cuphead.
You know that reviewer that played Cuphead?
I saw that clip.
That's what I feel like right now!
Maybe I should go work for IGN.
Is this in my future?
Okay.
Wait, what?
Oh!
Come on!
It's not that hard!
Yes!
Yeah!
Ah!
Oh!
We made it!
Wow!
Okay.
We're gonna go save the game.
Immediately.
Shut up, phone!
I didn't talk to you.
Alright, so...
So what is it with this dude anyway, huh?
Wait, wait!
I found a key, didn't I?
A travel egg!
Oh!
A special sound occurred!
Can't open that one.
Oh!
Ah!
Now we're here.
What a little secret!
Very nice.
Um...
I wanna go back up though, I'm not done.
I wasn't done.
With that area.
Okay, whatever.
Let me, uh, go back.
Nice.
Now, to go back to the egg...
We have to go to...
Bear one.
So bear with me.
Whoop!
And then right.
See you later, Brian!
Yeah!
Let's fucking go!
Wait.
The cuckoo happened just now.
I didn't pay attention.
Maybe this, uh...
Uh...
Wait, is that a cuckoo?
I don't know what a cuckoo looks like.
I know it's a bird.
Top.
Is this real life or a dream?
Oh, it has the little smoke effect on it.
Oh, that's nice.
Ooh.
What is this for?
Oh!
What?!
You can dig?!
Okay.
Rain egg.
I am digging this.
Actually, no pun intended.
There's no way.
I'm going through every single screen in this game and I'm gonna dig.
How do I know if it's diggable?
Need that.
I don't understand the system with the extra hearts.
Sometimes I get extra hearts, sometimes I don't.
Okay, that's not destroyed.
Okay.
Well...
We have a top.
Surely that will come in handy.
Let's go find some spots that can possibly be dug.
With the top.
Actually, wait a minute.
I think I see the type of material that can be dug.
No.
It's slower in weeds.
Also, you know what?
Let's take a break here.
It's been like two hours.
Five minute break.
I'll see you guys soon.
All right.
Here we go.
Nope, nope, nope, nope.
That's not the game.
That's the game.
There we go.
We got the top.
And it's time to...
Check out potential...
Floor plans that we can unearth.
I don't...
Or I can't think of any off the top right now.
In the world where I would like to destroy the floor.
Maybe down here.
The main room.
They gonna fall down?
Nope.
Okay.
I wanna see which blocks can be dug.
Speaking of dug.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Give me that.
None of these, huh?
Oh, that falls down.
Okay.
Wait, maybe this?
Nope.
Not that one.
The good news is it travels on its own.
You can just test everything.
Let's see what it does.
Ha!
It's stuck there.
Okay.
Can I hurt you with this?
Whoops.
Maybe we can hurt these guys.
Get hurt!
Ah, I don't think so.
Oh, you can throw it!
Ah, okay.
That's huge.
Oh, shit.
Can I dig in the water?
Of course not.
Why would you think that?
That doesn't even make sense.
Oh, not this room.
Oh, you know what?
Maybe this will dig for me, like, down there.
Oh, that is so useful!
Thank you.
That's incredible.
Now I can destroy all this.
Because I want to.
Let's get it out of here.
Right.
This place.
Oh, yeah.
Scary enemies.
We don't need them.
Uh, okay.
Can I dig anything here?
Fuck, I should have paid attention to what the block type was.
Oh!
Okay, so it looks like any other block!
Fuck!
What?
I literally can't see a difference.
Actually, I can.
It looks a little more, uh...
layer-y.
Yeah, that's definitely layer-y.
I think I see.
I understand.
Okay.
That's why I put a skull there.
I remember.
Oh!
I also have a question mark up there, for some reason.
I just came from there.
What is...
Why is there a question mark up there?
Oh!
Right.
So, I wanna go back up here.
I think.
Maybe.
Now, it's gonna be really difficult to keep track of these blocks.
So, this one looks like it can be destroyed.
It has these, uh... layers.
Nevermind.
I'm wrong.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Oh!
I see some!
Watch this!
I see it!
What?!
This little block below me!
You know what I mean?
What?
That totally looked like it was destructible.
Shit.
Can I destroy walls with this?
Okay, well, uh...
I still don't know where to go.
Where can I possibly use a top?
Is there an obvious, uh, break through the floor here?
Area?
I'm so lost in this game.
I don't know where to go.
That's where I'm at right now.
I feel like I've explored pretty much the whole area, or map.
But there's probably a tiny little pixel somewhere with an access to somewhere I haven't been yet.
You know?
I see something here.
Maybe?
Let's try and check that out.
Yeah, I can climb up there.
Dig for me.
Dig for me!
No digging, okay.
Yeah.
Then we go up to the right.
Oh shit.
Like, okay, so what?
The next one is 64 eggs?
How the fuck am I gonna find 64 eggs?
They must be superbly hidden.
Because I have no idea where they could possibly be.
Oh.
Nevermind.
Oh!
S-Metal!
S-Metal?
What does that mean?
S-Metal.
Sure.
Why not?
I do love me some S-Metal in the morning.
Actually, it's the afternoon here, but...
So, for some reason I didn't...
Properly explore this place.
No!
That's right.
None of that.
Let me spin you round, round, round.
Find dig spots for me.
None, eh?
Okay.
I can definitely make my way up there.
I see a little...
spot.
Wait, that gave me a blue heart!
Okay, here we go!
We're finally finding something new.
Blocked.
Okay, so...
Yeah, I see.
I see.
But I can't possibly...
provoke you to go left, can I?
Unless I do it from...
below?
Oh, shit.
Not what I had in mind.
Go back in here.
Like this.
Let's try another path.
Too dark to see the map.
Is there a candle in here?
Is that a candle in the center?
I can't tell.
It...
Yeah!
It is!
It did the blinking.
Ah!
Nice!
Okay, much better.
That gave me another blue heart!
I don't understand.
So, wait a minute.
This one should be solvable now, I think.
Like this right here?
There's no way it's not solvable.
Down!
Okay.
Ah!
Shit.
Ah, wait, wait!
I think I understand.
Chase it!
He should be right above me, right?
Chase that.
He probably pressed the button at this point.
Hopefully that works.
Brian!
Whoops.
How come he's not even reacting to my thing here?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
There we go!
Okay, now!
Brian!
I need you to go...
Okay, so here we go.
Chase it!
You know you want to!
That should do it.
And then...
Up we go.
I'm so bad at platforming.
Ah, Brian!
You motherfucker!
Okay, um...
Here.
I play flute to the left, that means you go left, okay?
How the hell...
Oh, wait, there's actually something above me here, it looks like.
Maybe that's something I can use.
Not that way, though.
Oh, but I can't enter!
Look!
It's blocked!
But it's blocked by a dice with...
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven sides?
No.
That's...
No, no, no way.
Wait, how do I get back down?
So it's something that has to happen in here, I guess.
Like, it's a self-contained puzzle.
Ah!
Brian, please.
Yep!
There we go.
Uh...
What else can we try?
Brian, Brian, Brian.
Brian is always such...
An annoying...
Thing, isn't it?
Uh...
Slinky!
Oh, wait, we gotta wake you up.
Wake up!
You like slinkies?
Firecracker.
Yay!
Okay, there it is.
Actually, that makes sense.
Heh, laissez-faire egg.
I wouldn't say I did that laissez-faire, but...
I would say it's unfair...
I'm kidding.
It's definitely some kind of fair.
A funfaire.
I...
Wait, wait, I see something.
You think you can fool me?
The master, uh...
Secret finder?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, wait, we've been here.
Hold on a minute.
At this point, I'm starting to think...
Is every dark area...
Map that I haven't discovered?
Because look how dense it normally is.
Look at all this.
For example, here, right?
And here.
That could be insane.
At some point, we're gonna get an item that will destroy these blocks here.
I don't know how, or why, or when.
But it's gonna happen.
Wait a minute.
This looks breakable.
I will never figure out what breakable looks like.
I can tell you that right now.
Never.
Hey, that made him change direction.
Oh, no, it didn't.
He followed me.
Okay, so we found something new there.
That's cool.
But I guess the goal is to get these fucking flames, but I can't get them.
Like, how do I get up there?
Shit!
Yeah, I don't know.
God, I'm so lost.
Maybe we can go look for those arrows again.
Man.
Yeah.
We gotta make this elevator go upwards somehow.
Question is how.
Am I supposed to look at differences in color on this map?
For example...
Uh, we gotta go here, right?
So we gotta somehow get up here with the elevator, but...
We haven't been able to jump from here to here.
But look at these pixels here.
They are like more white than the surrounding ones.
Maybe this can be...
Opened somehow.
There's also this.
Uh, where am I now?
There.
Oh god, just getting there is gonna be a nightmare.
Actually, we're not that far off.
It's travelable.
I guess.
Yeah, go up here.
Actually...
That.
Yeah, straight up.
But this path was blocked, wasn't it?
Maybe I can dig here.
Go in the little hole there.
Okay, you don't want to go in.
Oh!
There we go!
Here we go!
Postmodern egg.
Okay, that's fancy.
But I still can't access here.
I was hoping that would unlock a shortcut through here.
Well, that's something.
And I did see the...
the blocks.
They did look different.
I can't remember that though.
Like...
No way.
Oh, it didn't give me a heart.
I think I gotta go one step above and then into there.
In fact, let's try to go up the whole...
like the elevator again.
Not really the elevator, but you know.
The big...
A well?
Maybe?
Is that what that is?
A well?
Animal well?
I was wondering when the well would show up.
Maybe that's what it is.
Animal well.
Okay, save here.
For sure.
For sure we're gonna save that.
And now...
None of this looks diggable.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, there's the path up.
Actually, this is not the way because we can't do it here.
Unfortunately.
The vines are in the way.
And this is blocked off too.
Can I somehow cut these vines in half?
With the top?
No.
Too bad.
Telephone...
Shit.
The only way to get in there is from all the way in the bottom.
Let's go to bear one.
God damn.
I wish I know where to go.
Yeah, that is 64 eggs up there, I'm pretty sure.
What the fuck?
That's impossible.
Actually, we're already halfway.
For some reason I thought the egg counter reset.
But of course it's not the case.
Now we gotta go up one here, and then right.
Oh, we can't.
Unless...
We can dig here somewhere.
Is there diggable material in here?
But this is the path.
Nevermind.
We gotta go one higher, so up here.
Here.
Well, you may as well throw that, uh...
thing anyway, right?
In case it hits something.
Maybe there's multiple, uh, types of diggable objects.
Or blocks.
I call them blocks, because I've, you know, I'm thinking about Minecraft right now.
With the digging.
Ah, the birds don't mind the top.
Yeah, so this is it.
We gotta go down.
Wait, no.
Oh.
Further down.
What was this?
This is it.
Oh.
God.
I guess we gotta go from here.
Was that how it worked?
Wasn't there a bird here?
Trying to mess with my day.
Yep.
Fuck!
How the fuck do I get up there?
Here.
There too, maybe?
Losing my mind here, man.
And the worst part is, when I get up there, I probably can't do shit anyway.
I just wanna test something.
But to get there, I gotta go through a million hoops.
And fucking recall memories from ten years past.
Left.
Up here.
Okay.
Ah!
Fucking vines!
I don't know what to do in this game, dude.
Where do I go?
This is really frustrating.
There's a flame right down here.
And I have no idea how to get to it.
I guess we can try to go back there and see if we can.
But to do that, we have to go on a whole ass journey.
Okay, so...
Uh...
Bear two, I guess.
And then we're gonna go...
Down over here.
Right.
And then this way.
Okay.
Down.
Wait a minute.
No, okay.
I thought I saw something.
Yeah.
Now that I'm here, I wanna go...
All the way to the left.
Actually, the egg would've been better, I guess, in that case.
The egg room.
Transportation.
Since we're here anyway, let's just go.
Left, left, left.
I'm still trying to look for those arrows on the map.
Or in the background.
Yeah.
Like, every screen I activate, I, like, scan it.
Somewhat, you know?
Just to see if there's any arrows.
Okay.
Right.
Can I even go down over there?
Let me, let me think.
It looks like I can.
So, let's check it out.
Wait a minute.
Right.
That's...
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I should experiment with the thing here.
There's so much breakable shit.
Okay.
Nothing there.
It broke?!
Wow!
I didn't think it could break.
My poor top!
Get down here.
Okay, at least these spikes are gone still.
And now that I'm here...
We go right...
Oh, no.
Don't do this.
Not this place.
There's gotta be a different way.
Left...
Left seems better.
Wait a minute.
Yeah.
Okay, so here we are.
Down this way.
Spinning top!
Didn't find anything.
Okay, there's a bird here.
It's really annoying.
Right, now we're here.
We're approaching.
We should be here now.
Now we gotta go up.
Reverse this guy.
Get reversed!
Okay.
But wait a minute.
These guys are going the wrong way now.
Um...
Do I have to go all the way up here?
You gotta be kidding me.
What is that bear...
One.
And then I gotta go for...
Oh, it's all the way up there.
So...
How do I even get up there?
I'm gonna keep going right.
This way.
Straight up.
Should work.
Here.
Eat the fucking bubble.
And now take me on a trip to where I need to go, please.
Thank you.
The only way to reverse the...
Reverse the horizontal movement of those thingies...
Is to be on the side that I can't get to.
Which is just...
Hilarious.
So this is the only way, it seems.
Wait a minute.
What is this...
Where the fuck am I now?
Oh, I read the map wrong.
I thought this room was the room you entered when you traveled with the fucking thingies here.
I swear to god, dude.
Can I even do anything in here?
Too dark to see the map.
I guess I'll just go out of here.
Wait, I forgot where that takes me.
Bum bum bum bum.
Wait, where am I going?
Oh.
Wait, what?
Oh, I thought my triangle was where I entered.
Wait, where the fuck did I go from?
Oh, wait, I went from here.
Didn't I?
This is so confusing right now.
I came from there.
There we go.
There's a back and forth right here, it seems.
But, of course, you can't go straight up here.
You'd have to go...
And then get there somehow, right?
No, never mind.
There's a little path there.
That works.
But I don't want to go back.
Oh, my God, dude.
I guess I can try and get this flame.
I'm close to it, it seems.
Like, it's obviously over here.
But you can't get up there.
You can't get up there.
Look at this.
It looks like something is completely missing there, but...
I feel like I've been there before and it just...
It's just a fucking bunch of dice on the wall.
Like, I'd love to play the game if I could fucking know where to go.
I just don't...
I'm just too bad at this game, it seems.
I can't figure it out.
I'd love to continue.
I have no clue.
Something's going on with the cat, obviously.
Also, we do have one more down here.
What was that one?
Let me check it out.
Right, I didn't mark this one.
So, what are you even...
What kind of creature are you?
Who the fuck knows?
You are a...
WTF, I guess.
Lizard.
L.
And that takes me to...
Here.
L.
Surely I'll see that.
Big L.
Big L, rest in peace.
That's a great wrapper.
If you didn't know...
Well, this is actually a pretty good way to get down here, I guess.
That's something.
Let me check this out again.
So how the hell do I reverse the horizontal down here when I can't get to the place where I reverse it?
Like what?
Okay.
Brute forcing works.
Great.
Progress.
Now eat this bubble.
Okay, we're back here.
Finally.
I'm sorry, I wish I could rescue you, but I have to find the three little arrows that are hidden somewhere in the game.
Randomly.
Okay.
Okay, so there's apparently an egg right below here, but...
Maybe we can dig something with this.
Oh, it broke it, okay.
Wow, immediately breaks.
I just needed it to fall all the way down.
Okay, that doesn't do anything.
Can I make it go...
into the other...
There we go.
Okay, nothing down there either.
Now it's going this way.
Is that what we want?
I don't even know what I'm doing here.
Maybe I look for diggable places.
Diggable planets.
This way.
There's still this button up there on the left.
So how do we...
reverse the elevator on the left?
The only way I know of...
is to...
touch the cat up here.
Right there.
But that's obviously not gonna happen, because then we can't get back down here.
Or can we?
Wait, I made an arrow here for some reason.
Let's check it out.
Why did I make an arrow?
Oh.
Right.
Because we're missing one of the...
Yeah.
Okay.
Let me specify that.
Needs...
arrows.
Wow.
Ah.
Oh, I thought it would light up if I...
had the sequence right up until x...
amount of tries.
Nice.
Aw, man.
Okay.
Break everything in case something happens.
What's happening here?
If that breaks...
I can't get up there.
I can go down below, but that will take me back up.
Maybe I need to...
Let me think.
They're going down right now.
So if I can...
get up...
to the room above...
Wait a minute.
What about this right here?
Something's going on there, no?
Wait a sec.
Let me reverse these.
If I go in here now...
It's currently going to the right.
It's going to the right.
I go up there.
I go back to the right.
Oh, but they're still going down right now.
Oh, that's fine.
That's fine.
Then we take that one up to there.
We reverse it.
We go left...
to come back down.
Okay, I may have a strategy here.
Okay.
Now we want to go this way.
And we go over here.
In my mind, this works, but...
I need to fulfill the prophecy, you know?
Also, there's a chest right there when I'm going through.
Like that can't...
Like that chest is very nearby.
Let's not get distracted though.
Bubble for you.
Back down.
Come on.
Oh, wait.
I forgot to fucking...
Back up.
Bubble.
Let me see that chest now.
So up, left, up, right, left.
Okay, there it is.
So what...
That looks to me like digging...
...needs to happen.
Okay, now we go like this.
Now we go over here.
And then we do the bubble to the left now.
Or we could have used frisbee, I guess.
Either works.
Let me go in...
Here.
And now this should go up.
Fuck yeah!
Okay, good.
But wait.
Now we gotta reverse this.
Reverse that one.
There.
Okay, that should do it!
I don't know what we're trying to do here anyway, actually.
It's just a place I haven't been yet.
Okay, we got it.
Let's not fuck this up.
Don't fuck it up now.
What?
What's the point of that?
I don't understand that.
Maybe to go back?
Oh shit.
Brother.
Okay.
Thank God.
Okay!
So wait, there is no third arrow?
Come on.
There's gotta be.
You can't just leave this...
Poor creature alone.
I refuse to believe that.
Save the game.
Thank you.
I've got a flapjack here.
Let's remove this now.
There we go.
Okay.
Alright, this is looking promising.
So we need to do four buttons here.
I think.
Also, keep an eye out for arrows.
That's what I'm doing right now.
Swans!
And there's a lake too.
Where am I going?
Oh!
There's more hanging.
I'm just happy I finally have a new place.
I'm grateful for that.
Th- I don't like that.
That's scary.
Um...
Are you gonna break free?
Please don't break free.
No?
Okay.
Oh, I can't get up there.
So we gotta come from the right.
I see.
Fuck.
Me.
Okay, I made it here so we can- Yup!
There we go.
What'd that do?
It's probably one of the buttons I need to press.
Man, they have you imprisoned here?
Pulling these...
Swan alongs?
Swans along?
Oh!
Oh, okay.
I see.
But I want you to go this way.
No, the other way.
There we go.
Yes.
Man, there's some- there's some really dark shit happening down here in the well.
The animal- oh no, it's one of these things.
Didn't I also get something?
This thing down there.
The...
Smeddle.
The Smeddle has to go in here, I'm pretty sure.
Cause where else would it go?
Now I gotta make this guy reverse.
Again.
Oh!
What?
Oh, what a secret little path.
Wow.
This is impossible.
Is it?
Yeah, this needs to be reversed.
But let's go click that button first.
Oh shit.
Man, this is really difficult.
I can't get in the hole!
Okay, there we go.
Something activated on the right.
I saw that.
Wait.
It doesn't stay down.
Wait, I'm stuck.
What the fuck do I do?
Kill me.
Okay.
Well, that was not a good idea.
We also haven't tried going down here yet.
Maybe we should try that.
Ah!
Okay.
I see.
Oh, that doesn't go back and forth.
Alright.
So we need to have all four of those...
pressed at the same time.
Okay, so we can press them by sliding against it.
I'm guessing this is also water.
Yeah.
It's hard to tell sometimes.
Oh, there's a button down there too.
I can't reach it like that.
I have to make this...
Whoops.
I gotta reverse this and then come back here, I think.
I didn't take damage from that.
That was weird.
Okay, so there you are.
I need you to go the other way now.
What does this button do, man?
Oh!
Sounds.
Let's go on a trip.
Up, up.
Good.
Ah!
There we go.
Am I safe just staying here?
It seems like it.
We're gonna press this button.
Turns them on, okay.
Hmm.
There we go.
Nice!
But wait, what did that do for me?
Hello?
Okay.
Um, sure.
More importantly though, maybe we can go to the right, or the left, while these are going to the right.
You know what I mean?
Like, in this configuration.
How would we do that?
That seems impossible.
Unless I have a slinky situation going on.
Can I distract you...
with the slinky?
No?
Wait a sec.
That's two.
You see that?
There's one light activated on him right now.
That's two lights.
So we leave a slinky here, maybe?
And then...
go in here, and then maybe if we activate another light, he will return on his own?
Maybe.
Whoops.
But what's going on with this here?
That's so mysterious.
Aw, crap.
Yeah, we gotta get there.
Yep!
Made it.
Nice!
Okay, so we pressed it.
Now they're going the other way.
Oops.
So I can come back.
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh my god, it fell on me!
Aw, bastard.
I released it!
Fucking fans.
So wait, is it free now?
I actually died from that.
Oh!
Oh, crap!
Fuck!
Oh no!
The other way!
Oh, I'm fucked.
I'm fucked.
I can't do anything.
Try to catch me now, bitch!
Shhh!
Okay.
Uh...
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
You like yo-yos!
Nope!
Okay.
Oh god.
Let me play you a soothing melody!
There.
Play with that.
How the fuck do I get out of here?
I can't do anything.
Okay, there we go.
You can't reach me.
Oh, shit balls.
I'm getting squished!
Oh my god!
Bro!
Run!
Fuck!
Oh yeah!
Yeah!
Oh, it pressed the buttons for me!
Oh my god!
That was heart...
inducing!
Heart stop inducing!
Jesus Christ!
This game is scary!
Got a blue heart.
We got a flame!
G flame!
Oh, the power of the G flame!
G unit!
We got it!
The swan flame!
It's flame!
Okay, and we have a, uh, shark here as well.
Oof.
Man.
Um...
What do I do with these flames?
I have three of them, actually.
I got three of them.
Wait, before I leave here, I just want to mark this.
Uh...
We have an...
An input there.
Let me check for secrets real quick.
While there's no monster anymore!
Monster's gone.
Now we can relax.
Okay, what is that?
Oh, that's just the water dripping.
Okay.
Maybe there's some Santa's secret here.
Nah, maybe not.
No.
So, all of these are not moving anymore.
I wonder if I locked myself out of something now.
OH-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh!
Look at that!
Fuckin' hell!
Uh, bop-bop-bop.
Uh, what was it?
Okay, uh, bop, bop, bop.
Beautiful!
Fuck yeah.
Okay.
I know, buddies, but I only have, uh, enough arrows for one of you.
And I'm sorry to say, you will not be chosen.
You have been weighed and you have been measured, and you have been found wanting.
I'm sorry!
Some of you have to die, so that the others of you may live.
Okay, so, I gotta get back up, I guess.
Here we go.
Oops.
Alright, buddy, you ready?
Let's go.
Let me see it.
Uh, bring the flute out.
What?
Wait.
Hold on.
Uh,
maybe I noted it down wrong.
I mean, it's pretty high-changing.
There's a chance of that, I guess.
Uh,
let's see.
Bop.
Is that right?
Down right, up, down right, down right, left.
That's what I have!
Maybe it's for a different cat.
Let me try these ones.
Wait, I fucked it up.
I tried to remember it.
Uh,
excuse me.
Okay!
We got one of them.
Okay, so...
You're free.
Come on, go.
You don't wanna leave?
Aw.
Oh, there we go!
Look, it's gone!
Okay, nice.
That makes me feel better.
Uh, you know what?
Actually, hold on.
We gotta go even further back.
Maybe there's more.
Let's keep looking for... for arrows.
Why is there a death... thing... oh, never mind.
I can't go back to the left, unfortunately.
That's pretty much impossible now.
But I can go up here.
No, I can't.
I'm really looking now.
Arrows... arrows... arrows... arrows...
Maybe in here?
I don't see anything.
Let's see where you take me.
Going up, up, up.
Okay.
Elevator?
Chest!
That was almost straight up.
Ooh!
Here we go.
Boom!
Blow it up.
Oh, we'd be blasting!
I love that effect.
I don't see any arrows.
Ooh, I know what's gonna happen here!
Oh, it broke already.
What?
Aha!
Yeah.
Blow that up.
God, it's so satisfying.
Let me just do that all day.
Okay, so now we're back here.
Okay.
Well, that's nice.
This is water.
Yeah.
Here.
Have a top.
How much you want to bet that that sound of something falling in is Billy Basso and his bathtub?
So where am I going now, is the question.
I guess we look for the last flame, right?
Flame, flame.
It's here.
So, obviously, the whole problem that I'm facing right now is this elevator situation.
That's the problem right now.
And I just don't know what to do about it.
We can access here, but we can't.
There's a big wall, it seems like, here with a hole in it.
But I've been there before, I'm pretty sure, and it's just dice.
Something goes in...
Oh, wait!
Oh, we gotta go here.
Let's check this out now.
That's what I want to do.
So we gotta go to bear one.
Right?
No, F1.
Formula One?
That's the best.
Okay.
That's this one, isn't it?
No, that's L.
Formula One is up here.
What's it called?
Fish One.
Oh, shit!
I'm...
Wait, what?
That's not F1!
What the fuck?
I messed up my map!
Was it F2?
Oh!
Shit!
Okay.
So where...
Where did I put my, um...
F...
Oh, there we go.
That's F1.
Okay!
Good to clear that up.
This is where I merged.
Just a little bud.
I call this move?
The Melania.
Ah!
I don't know if I jumped into water.
Shit.
Recess.
Okay, so down.
Right.
Up.
There it is.
Please work.
Actually, I have no reason to think it's gonna work, because last time we needed a shard.
Oh!
It worked!
The Smedal!
Nice!
Okay, we're making big progress right now.
This is what I was looking for.
I was so frustrated for, like, almost an hour, not knowing where the hell I should go.
This is...
This is it.
This is it right here.
This is what I've been looking for.
Um, okay.
Let's try and figure this out.
We got bad boys on the bottom.
Missed it.
Ah!
Right in the butt.
Did I just mess myself up?
What am I doing here?
Let me try and dig.
The bad guys don't care about the dig.
Fine.
That's a spike, you idiot!
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm over here now.
Is that just going to continue?
I don't want it to continue.
Ah!
Sweet.
And now, we go right.
Where am I going?
Oh yeah, over there.
I guess I can...
Uh, can I...
Can I...
Oh.
Okay.
That...
Oh!
Oh shit!
Saved.
That was almost a death spiral.
Now, this doesn't help me very much.
Oh, that's a roof!
Okay.
I thought I could, uh...
Traverse that.
Just down here.
Oh!
It's just a different way to get up here.
How do I actually do this?
Not like that.
Oops, I'm low HP now.
This is bad.
That's not going to work.
Ah!
Fuck.
Um...
Oh shit, I'm back here?
Wow.
That's quite...
Far back.
Go on a trip again.
Okay, so we blew all this up already.
Blew...
Wait, what?
Oh yeah.
This...
Like, there's gotta be a telephone here somewhere.
I guess I didn't need to do that, but, you know, I wanted to.
Oh wait!
Ah!
Of course.
Just go back.
Okay.
So we decided it was fish...
Two.
That's the one.
Right?
Yes.
Oh my god, what a path to take.
I cannot die again.
No more dying.
I like the reflections of this ladder in the water.
That's nice.
Okay.
Good.
Man, there's gotta be like...
What is this?
Something up there?
Why is it glowing?
Okay, maybe nothing.
Give me a telephone!
Dude, I have such trouble...
Like, look at this.
Where I'm walking right now, it looks like I can jump to the left.
It doesn't look like a wall to me at all.
And first try.
Boom.
That's how you do it.
Ah!
I see the problem.
Fucking vines, dude.
Fucking nihilists.
And Isaac.
It's mine now.
Thank the lord.
Descend slowly.
Into the spikes.
Whoop!
That was close.
Wait, how do I...
There we go.
Careful.
No, go!
Good.
Now we descend.
That's a snake!
Is it coming for me?
Is it crazy that I want to slinky the snake?
Look at the staircase it's making.
Are you actually coming up for me?
Okay, you're not.
So what is the deal here?
I see, uh...
I see beehives?
Yeah.
There's bees in here.
That snake is probably not friendly.
Wait, I see secret.
Wait, I can walk on him!
Ah-ha!
That's awesome.
Secret spotted, but we need some kind of four, uh...
foursome configuration.
Let me just fish a little bit, do you mind?
Ha-ha-ha!
Whoa!
The yo-yo went wild!
Whoops!
Okay, wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I mean, I could just...
What?
What happened?
Oh no, I'm back here!
What the fuck?
I had full HP!
Goddammit!
Okay, up here.
Down.
Okay, I thought the snake was friendly.
Never trust animals, guys.
This is the lesson in this game.
Fucking storks left and right and dolphins and shit.
They will fuck you up.
Your arm will be broken.
It'll be in pieces.
And they're done with you.
Okay, now we just ladder down.
Here.
Also, what is this weird trophy-looking thing right here?
You see that?
I've been seeing this at certain places.
Okay, let's just get this done.
Let's not interact with the snake any more than we need to.
Let him do his thing.
We're gonna be on our way.
Let's stay away from me!
Dammit.
What?
Oh, the vines.
Right.
Boink.
Okay.
Oh, we got a Paraguay!
That means no bubbles for me.
Like, what a bully.
Just an all-around jerk to be doing that, you know?
Remote?
What?
No way.
Yo, that effect is incredible-looking.
The way they bounce off the walls.
I would love to see the code for that.
It's probably not that complicated, but it's-it's really neat.
Oh, man, it's neat.
It's really neat.
Holy shit.
Wow.
Ha-ha!
Oh, man.
I-reminds me of Subnautica.
That one, uh...
sonar thingy, right?
Sends out a ping.
In fact, this is what it looks like when you use a remote in real life.
You just can't see it.
Like, it's spreading out like this in all directions and being reflected left and right and stuff.
It's very complicated.
It's-it's really cool.
It's just at the speed of light, of course.
So it feels instant.
Uh...
Wait a sec.
What's this down here?
Differently colored walls?
What's that all about?
A remote.
I cannot believe that.
Dig here.
No digging?
Okay.
Yeah, save.
That's fine.
What is going on there?
Like, that wall is suspiciously colored.
Something goes in slot.
Oh, yeah, right.
That's the thing.
Let me write something here.
Color.
Wall.
Something with rainbow.
Oh, you bastard.
Right.
Oh.
Dude, this is actually so freaking cool.
I can do this anywhere, I guess?
That's insanity.
Oh, I- I see.
So where am I supposed to go here?
Like, am I just gonna go back up?
It feels like there should be some kind of shortcut back.
Just, you know, metagame perspective here.
We're, uh...
Oh!
We're playing, Snake!
Wait, what?
Oh!
Oh, excuse me.
We control it!
Look at that!
Oh, yeah!
Bro.
Incredible.
Wow.
You know, I could play with you, but I could also just not.
So, see ya.
Like, you are brilliant, but, uh, I like this.
Iridescent egg.
Dude, that was...
That was...
That is really cool.
So, wait.
Can I...
Can I remote control all the animals?
I want to remote control a chihuahua so bad, actually.
Holy shit.
Imagine that.
Dude, imagine a chihuahua remote controlled.
That's crazy.
Um...
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, actually.
I was thinking maybe we can control the snake into the next room and then have the snake eat at the colored wall, but why would that make sense?
It doesn't make any sense.
Never mind.
But, uh, here's the thing.
We now have this remote control.
Where the fuck can I use this to my advantage?
Probably up here.
Right there.
That...
Oh, that looks doable.
We gotta go up there.
That is bear one.
Boom!
That was the fastest bear one I've ever done.
Oh, man.
I hope we get to see a chihuahua, actually.
And I get to remote control it.
That would be sick.
Uh, Brian, I need you to...
Actually, don't move.
That doesn't matter.
Can I go up somehow?
Yeah, over there.
This way.
Whoops.
Also, we gotta look for breakable floors.
Yes?
Oh, dude.
Dude!
Oh, the...
The chests are beeping!
I love when they do that.
Let me remote control the elevator!
Oh, my God.
Okay, calm down.
This is what we practiced for.
This is what we've been practicing for.
Save the game.
Open the, uh...
Thingy.
Whoops.
Beep-eep-eep-eep-eep-eep-eep-eep-eep-eep-eep-eep-eep-eep.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, I love that.
Let me quickly do this.
Oh!
I control everything!
Look at me!
The master of, uh...
Radiation.
Infrared radiation, by the looks of it.
I think that's also what they use in remote control, isn't it?
Let's go down here.
Wait, what?
No, no, no, no, no.
Up here.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe I can do this now.
Well...
Wait, wait, wait.
What was the issue here?
No, wait.
What?
Why is there a hole in the map?
Why won't that turn invisible?
What?
Isn't that one of those...
Look at the wall!
It looks like one of those.
But I guess...
You know what?
Dude.
It's probably coded in a way that...
Things will not actually activate until...
The actual wave has reflected off a surface and reached the actual pixel of the receiver.
I bet you that's how this works.
Like...
And it's probably not even needed to do something like that.
But I guarantee it's how it works.
Just because...
I can see this guy just...
Coding that for fun.
Then again, I could be wrong.
So, there's gotta be a way to remote control this elevator.
You can't tell me there's not.
Like, this is so obvious.
Oh!
Look at the receiver!
You see the...
The little...
Bibbidi-bobbidi-bop!
It's there!
Okay, okay.
Now, can I remote while I'm on this?
Oh!
I can't!
Yes, I can!
Because I'm a god.
Chocolate egg...
Goes in my mouth.
Oh, wow.
I love this.
Okay, good, good, good.
Oh, man.
What if I stand in the wall?
I wanna become one with the wall!
Behold!
The wall!
It is I!
Okay.
Uh...
Funnily enough, I'm not hitting the receiver on the left, so I thought...
Maybe that's not how he's coding it, then.
Unless there's a hitting receiver in here.
It's probably just whatever's on my screen, right?
Yeah, actually, that's probably what happens.
Um...
Let's go back...
Oh!
No!
Rip!
Fuck.
God, this is the walk of shame.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
The swan!
Look at that!
The swan is active.
Let me remote control you guys.
Oh, there's...
It looks like there's four animals here, so it's probably...
There's not gonna be a chihuahua.
And even worse, I'm not gonna be able to remote control it.
That's funny.
Um...
Okay, let's...
Let's, uh, try this again.
Oh, man.
It's still...
Going down.
That bastard.
Okay, but...
Wait.
Hold on, hold on!
Okay, we're fine.
Remote control time.
Let me through!
I command you with my remote!
Motherfucker.
Okay.
But, like...
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
This...
I can probably remote here.
And if I can remote that, maybe I can remote this...
To get in here.
You know?
We need, uh...
Bear 2.
Chihuahua!
In my tummy...
Left.
Actually, we should be, uh...
Remoting every room.
Beepedebop!
I'm coming for that slop.
Let me, uh...
Mess with your inner ear.
There we go.
What?
How did I just take damage?
Oh, I jumped into the...
The bad guys.
Makes sense.
Nice.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Up here.
Yeah, let's check this out.
This gotta work.
I think it does.
No!
No.
Don't do this to me.
Oh!
We can see just through the walls!
Well, I mean, I would've...
I would've gone here anyway at some point, because you can see an opening.
Oh, this is gonna be so helpful.
What a great item.
Dude, I was about to shit on the game design here, with the hidden stuff, but this alleviates that issue I had with the game.
It really does.
This is fucking great.
Okay.
So...
What?
How the hell do I proceed?
Uh, let's investigate this wall here.
It's been bugging me.
Bear 3.
Bear 3 is...
Where?
There.
Top left.
There's a hole in the wall!
I don't remember being here.
What?
Ah, you bastard.
Fine!
I'll play your game.
Wait, how do I play your game?
Oh, I see.
I see.
Sneaky.
Oh!
Don't get squished.
Yeah, okay.
I understand.
We just gotta be fast here.
So, one, two, three, four, five.
That can't be right.
One, two.
And...
Blubber for breakfast.
It's what I will punish myself with for that.
Go!
What?
How?
Wait, what?
Actually, how?
How?
Huh?
Hmm.
I can't make that jump.
That's...
an impossible jump.
Oh, no, it's not.
If I jump when it's a little lower, then it works.
Actually, wait a minute.
Yeah, I think the timing is correct here.
I'm gonna be high up.
Look.
Hey!
And then...
Now!
Yeah!
Okay, fantastic.
Good shit.
We got leprechauns in the bottom.
Posing for something.
Probably their IG.
And these weird wolf...
Not penguins.
Fucking dolphins.
That needs a key.
Okay, you know what?
Let's actually mark that.
I guess it's already kind of marked.
Key.
Don't get it twisted.
Chest spotted!
Digging, engage.
Digging, disengaged.
Uh...
Come here.
Beepity boop.
Chest has been spotted.
How do I access...
said chest?
Let's mark it.
The chest symbol is going to be...
The chest symbol.
Boom.
I know.
It makes sense.
Oh, that's a spike.
Right.
Uh, let's...
Ah!
Stay out of the way!
Whoops.
Didn't mean to fall all the way down.
Thank you.
Man.
Why do I need to open that door...
When I can just...
Not go through the door?
Hello?
Can I open it from the back?
That door is useless.
Oh, look at that.
Whoops.
A secret...
To be sure.
What's the point of that?
Can I wedge something in between?
Okay.
Maybe not.
Yo, what ha...
Uh...
Welder...
Welcome to the Hydraulic Press Channel.
Let's see what happens to the Slinky.
Okay.
Slinky is gone.
Shit.
That does that.
Wait.
What is the point of this?
Like, what am I trying to do here?
I don't understand.
What am I...
Am I trying...
Oh, I'm trying to get to that...
Rotator down there, but for what reason?
This is too much for me.
I can't handle it.
What is the point of that?
A square is there...
And then comes to two lines.
Uh...
Oh!
Oh, I...
I fucked it up.
Oh, no.
Am I stuck?
I'm not.
Okay.
I understand.
Hurry!
Yeah!
Oh!
I almost got squished.
Yeah, I made it just in time.
A raw egg!
Going in raw.
Whoop.
Very good.
Okay.
And that was that chest.
We can remove that now.
Why did I put an arrow here?
Oh!
Because it's from the bottom.
Let me, uh...
Ring up the guys.
Okay.
No response.
I guess it's just a way to get across.
Maybe.
Uh...
But wait a sec.
Ah!
Bastard.
Good enough for me.
Boop!
Oh!
You know what?
Fuck that.
I can do it myself.
Thank you very much.
A rabbit.
Oh!
We're finally here with the button!
Thank God!
It only took a million years.
Remote.
What is that stuff above me?
It's like a fortress.
It's a flap.
Jack.
Shit!
Alright.
Fine.
I'll go back, I guess.
God damn it.
I did not want to do that.
That was not my intention at all.
Okay.
Just double checking.
I love that effect so much!
Oh God!
It's beautiful.
It's perfect.
Whoops.
Oh my God.
What is the procedure again?
Okay.
Fine.
I'll do it the old-fashioned way.
That door up on the left is so useless, it's laughable.
Makes me laugh.
Ha ha ha.
I'm kinda stuck here.
No.
I'm way too impatient right now.
Ah ha!
Can't fool me.
Oh, that's what these are!
They're remote towers!
Look!
I just realized.
I mean, I saw the dot before, but...
I didn't realize it was on top of one of those.
That makes sense.
Now, that switch up there?
What exactly are we dealing with?
What is that?
Ha!
It's the manual one.
I have a remote.
Bitch!
So, these are flapjacks.
Right?
So, if I were to...
Yep!
Why is this a thing?
Okay.
Well, that didn't really do much.
Oh, I thought that would change the thing.
What is the point of this?
These are African lynxes.
I don't know about Africa, but...
They're lynxes.
Mdisk!
It's an Mdisk shrine.
Wait, what?
It's an Mdisk shrine?
Oh, we gotta bring the evil disc here!
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
That's what needs to happen.
Wait, why is...
Some things are beeping red when I do this.
Others are not.
Isn't that weird?
Like...
The gray matter in the back is beeping red when I click this.
Uh, okay.
Let's mark it.
Needs...
E...
C.
Okay.
Now, we still have this down here.
Oh, there it is!
Oh, but we can't enter.
We gotta come from above.
Right, okay, I see.
I understand.
Let's also remove this guy.
So, uh...
Here it is.
Oh, god.
We gotta plan our attack here.
How are we gonna do that?
Can I just go...
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
Right after?
Or what?
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
And then bear three.
And then right.
Sounds easy enough.
All right, let's do it.
Let's go to bear one.
Bear one...
Okay, bear one is up here.
Yeah, it's right above me.
So, yeah, we gotta go right first.
You know, it definitely helps the more you traverse the map.
It gets a little more ingrained in your mind where things are.
But, man, this map is so convoluted.
It's borderline too much for my brain to keep track of.
Because it's just...
Like, I'm not very good at navigation in games like this.
It's so easy for me to forget, like, a little path or something.
Why did I make a circle here?
Let's move that.
Am I too high up?
Wait, why did I make a skull here?
Is that where it is, truly?
Wait, I think I went too far.
Yeah, it's here, isn't it?
There you go, buddy.
Also, I should be doing this.
Every room.
Ping the elders.
Is it really down there?
That feels wrong.
Maybe I mismarked it.
Oh, no, I didn't.
I didn't.
Okay, so...
Yeah, M-disc.
Yeah.
M-disc.
Fuck you, bitch.
Bear three.
Go!
Oh, shit, it's fast!
I thought it wouldn't get here that fast!
Uh, remember your training.
I-I think.
Go!
Bubble!
Wait, what just happened there?
What was that?
Something like that old man.
Fuck!
Oh, okay, we gotta go through that.
Don't you ill me!
Woo!
That sounds ridiculous!
Oh, my God!
Are you kidding me?
Go!
What the fuck?
Bro, it's impossible.
That little piece of shithole we have to get into...
...can suck it!
Wait, wait, wait.
One, two, three.
Fuck all y'all!
Oh, my God.
You're fast.
You're fast!
It's over!
We're done!
Oh.
It's over.
Wow!
Jump, you bastard!
Okay, okay, good.
Good.
Right, right, right, right, right.
Do the thing.
Whoa, you're fast!
Oh, God.
Good.
Bubble!
Motherfucker!
What do you mean?
Oh, Jesus fucking Christ.
Oh!
Oh, it's over.
It's just kill me.
Kill me!
God damn it.
Dude, it's so stressful!
I can't do it.
I can't even remember the melody!
See you, bitch.
Come on.
Swift but cautious.
Go.
Fantastic.
That's beautiful.
Beautiful.
Why are you so fast all of a sudden?
You're not supposed to be that fast.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
The fucking bubble wand wasn't equipped!
Man,
fuck off.
You know what?
I'm probably not even supposed to do this.
Nah, I have to, right?
For sure, it's this.
So I go here.
One, two, one, two.
Fucking...
One, two!
One, two.
One, two, three.
One, two, three, one, two.
What?
Where's it gone?
One, two, three.
One, two.
Good.
Here we go.
Boom!
Boom.
One, two, three.
One, two.
Bubble one, it's ready.
Yes.
Good.
Smooth.
Up you go.
What?
It's impossible.
How did I get up there earlier?
I don't understand.
It's impossible.
Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna do my own thing.
My own thing is not working.
Nah, just kill me!
Kill me!
Just fucking kill me.
Fucking kill me.
Come on, let's try again.
Oh my god, dude.
This is so difficult.
And it doesn't vibe with my brain at all, because I get so freaking anxious with this bastard following me.
Okay.
One, two.
We're gonna try something new here.
Fuck the normal things.
Doing my own thing.
Bubble one for the win!
Oh god.
No, it's over.
It's over.
Quick!
What did you do to the right?
I said left!
Ah, it's bullshit.
I fucking... Input reading was wrong.
Like, I wasn't doing it that way.
God, I hate this.
This is so creepy.
It's insane.
I can't stand this fucking thing following me.
Why are you doing to the right?
Oh, come on, man.
It's fucking broken the inputs here.
Fuck, come on.
Don't fuck it up now.
What?
Wait, what?
This way, this way.
Yes!
The lynxes of Africa have been lit.
Unlit.
Lit.
The lynxes of Africa have been... Unlit.
That's what you get, bitch.
God, that feels good.
That was so difficult.
It was so difficult.
Wow.
I think I made a mistake trying to bubble board my way at the end there.
It wouldn't work, you know?
What is this up top right?
There's something up there still.
Oh, man.
But, boys, it's satisfying finally getting that.
Wow.
Yes!
Here we go.
Bop!
Flame.
How do I get out?
There's a button.
That's probably the way out.
Okay.
We've never been here before.
This is new.
Still can't make it reverse.
Well, I guess we go all the way down.
Something's gonna happen now for sure, though, when we put in the last flame.
Oh, there.
Oh!
Haha.
Would you look at that?
Wait, what?
Oh, that was here the entire time.
It's a dog.
Oh, look at the little thing he's inside of.
You see this?
This is what we need to put in the slots we found.
I think.
It's gonna make things rotate.
But, so what?
We gotta find a little dog?
In a...
In a hamster wheel?
Wait, maybe it's a hamster.
No, that's a dog, right?
Just because it's a hamster wheel, I mean.
Um, okay, so, so...
What is the...
What's going on here?
Oh!
Yes!
Oh, yeah.
Let me see if there's more I can do here with this.
Right, that one.
Come on.
Oh!
Oh, wait, we've been here.
Next one.
Chest!
It's a big egg.
It doesn't fit.
Oh!
Another chest hiding in there.
Let me mark that.
Actually, not like that.
With this.
Boom.
Somewhere around there.
In fact, can we...
do something about that now?
Blow it up!
Mello!
No?
Okay.
Okay, so we're here now.
Let's go further up.
Ah!
Oh!
I...
Okay.
That's death.
I thought I could go up there.
Well.
Rip.
Did I just, uh...
No, I still have all my things.
Okay.
Eat that.
We gotta go down here now.
Yeah.
Return disc?
I don't have a disc on me anymore, do I?
Oh.
Weird.
Why...
Why can I do that?
Maybe I can do it later, uh...
In relation to another puzzle.
Maybe that'll do something, you know?
Okay.
Jump down.
Here we go.
Uh, save the game.
Okay.
What is the last animal?
Oops.
It's the dog.
Okay, we're gonna do the dog next time.
That's a good place to stop.
I'm gonna activate the dog next time.
Cliffhanger.
Man, that was a rough one for me.
I got so frustrated halfway through because I couldn't find my way through the game.
But once I did...
So much better.
And the remote?
Incredible.
No, I'm not good with stress.
I've never been.
I can't handle any type of stress.
Time to eat tortillas.
Actually, I also have leftovers of tacos.
I'm gonna eat those tonight.
Always finding the hardest solution possible.
I...
It's...
I'm not doing that on purpose.
I don't know how...
How, uh...
I mean, it would be interesting to see...
Actually, I can't wait to see someone else play this game.
I'm gonna watch a Let's Play of this when I'm done.
I need to see...
How the hell people handle some of these things.
I gotta see it.
Did you hydrate enough today?
I did not.
I should have...
Drank more.
I keep forgetting.
Thank you for scheduling.
Oh...
Yeah.
Usually I don't do it, though.
Because I don't know when I'll...
Be wanting to play a game.
It's like...
I can't buy groceries for a whole week.
Because I don't know what I'll...
Be wanna eating on Friday.
That was a terrible English sentence.
But I don't know what I wanna eat on Friday, right?
When it's Monday.
So I just buy things for the day, usually.
Unless I have leftovers.
I'm the same way with this, you know?
Please don't watch pirate software?
Why not?
Seeing you're stuck in this game is 100 times more frustrating than seeing you're stuck in blueprints.
I would say I'm better at blueprints than I am at this game.
This game combines...
So, here's the thing, guys.
I am not very good at puzzle games...
Like, full stop.
It's just not one of my strengths.
I'm definitely better at different games.
And this is a 2D platformer, which is something I'm not good at either.
So combining those two is just...
Disaster recipe for me.
When it comes to difficulty.
I thought you can't buy groceries, no money, so you stream for money.
Well, yeah.
I guess so.
You're not wrong.
I do earn my money through this.
We saw that with Chance of Sanar.
Well, that game is...
I don't know.
That game was really fun.
I thought I was decent at it.
I wouldn't say I was that bad at that game.
It was...
It was okay.
Like, put me in games like...
StarCraft.
Then I'm gonna kick ass, you know?
I'm definitely someone who is slow at learning, but I'm very good once I get good at it.
You know what I mean?
It just takes a while for me.
The O in Oliver stands for over-fucking-thinking!
Yeah, probably.
You're not wrong.
I tend to do that a lot.
Lots of people don't figure out the bubble jump thing at all?
What?
That was like the first thing.
It was like...
Immediately came to my mind.
That's what I had to use it for.
That's so crazy how...
Brains work differently, right?
Frank.
Cave story.
Let me check it out.
Is that an old game?
2011?
Nice.
That's not old.
I'm talking...
1998.
Or something.
Or maybe it is old and they just re-released it.
I could be wrong.
It has those graphics?
Okay.
The graphics are definitely not something very interesting, I will say.
But that's how it is with the old games, right?
In fact, I want to play the Prince of Persia, the old one.
I used to play that with my friends back when I was like eight years old on a common computer.
Like...
And we would take turns.
It was actually really difficult.
That was so difficult.
I remember that.
I don't think I ever beat it.
I may only have played some of the levels and stuff, because we used to take turns and it wasn't always my turn at the computer and stuff.
Yeah, I think they made a new one recently.
2004.
The original freeware version of Cave Story.
Oh, okay.
Wait, old Harry Potter games?
I don't think I've ever played a Harry Potter game.
Are they good?
Also, a recent one came out.
I kind of want to play it.
I do like Harry Potter.
I like the world, the characters, the stories.
It's pretty good.
Gives me good childhood feelings, you know?
With limitations, it really comes creativity.
That is so true, Crusader.
You know what's funny?
I've been thinking about that for a while.
Like, for many years.
That I always seem to do better when I have less tools.
Because it forces me to think outside the box a lot of the times.
And not just in terms of games.
Also in terms of, like, coding.
Or, you know, other things in life.
It really...
It really does something for the creativity.
My god, am I the only Gen X here?
I don't know.
What is Gen X?
When were you born?
Mid-1960s?
Late-1970s and early-1980s.
Well...
Okay.
1980 here.
So you're like 12 years older than me.
I'll soon be there.
1971?
1970.
That's actually pretty cool.
I didn't realize we had...
So many, uh...
Distinguished, older people in chat.
Not...
I'm saying you're old.
40 is not that old.
I'll be 40 soon.
Do you play them if you don't want people to jump you?
Wait, what?
Do not play them if you don't want people to...
What?
I'm confused by what...
What do you mean by that?
Not that distinguished either.
Okay.
Old equals my age plus 5.
You know what?
I would say so, yeah.
That's a pretty good one.
I will agree to that.
93?
I'm 92.
So you're a little younger than me.
I don't know anything about her politics and I don't care.
It's like people were hating on...
What was it?
Tom Cruise?
For Scientology at some point.
And I was just like, I don't care what Tom Cruise does in his private life.
I just want to see him run fast and shoot people in movies.
And then I'm happy.
I really don't care.
I don't have brain...
Ram to care about that stuff.
What if he runs fast in real life too?
That sentence is so funny.
Someone made a compilation once of all the times that Tom Cruise ran in movies.
And you know what?
He's been running a lot.
And he's really good at running in movies.
Yeah.
Some say he's still running.
I mean, he is.
He's still making movies.
He recently made one...
What was it?
The newest Mission Impossible.
He's doing the crazy stunts, right?
Yeah, it is an oddly specific compilation.
It's just like...
Oh God, what's his name?
The guy who says...
Wow.
Someone made a compilation of all the times he said that in all of his movies.
Oh, he's so good in Magnolia.
That's true.
He's incredible in that.
Yeah, Owen Wilson.
That one.
Or that guy, yeah.
Owen Wilson.
Makes me want to watch Wedding Crashers again.
That's such a fun movie with Owen Wilson.
And Vince Vaughn.
That's such a great duo.
I wish they made more movies together.
Yeah, Bloop.
That's why I don't...
I don't want to talk about politics at all.
Like, it's just not what I do.
I just want to play video games and forget about all that.
That's why I do it, right?
Among other reasons.
I love video games.
I just want to do that.
That's what it's all about.
There's other spaces for that, right?
Minority Report.
That's a great one, man.
That's a really good one.
Spielberg doesn't make movies like that anymore, I feel like.
Like, that era is over for him.
Yeah, exactly, Crusader.
I agree.
You know, Frank, I was thinking of playing some scary game soon.
Because it is Halloween.
When does Halloween start?
What is the official start?
Is it the 31st?
It is the 31st, isn't it?
Yeah, okay.
Maybe, like, Little Nightmares or something?
That's not a terribly long game, right?
Or some other scary game?
Or horror game?
People have been asking for that one specifically for a while.
Oh yeah, Amnesia.
I've been thinking about that one, too.
The Dark Descent, though, I already played, Sparf.
I completed it.
That was way before I started streaming, though.
But there's other Amnesia games.
The Bunker, yeah.
Actually, someone gifted me the Bunker at some point.
I haven't played it.
But I have it ready to go.
It's in the chamber.
Or a machine for pigs.
Yeah, I haven't played that either.
That would be the next logical one.
That comes after the Dark Descent.
Luca, I don't know exactly how far I am.
I don't know if you played the game, but I have...
I just got the last flame.
If that tells you anything.
Yes, I did play Soma, Sparf.
Also played it before streaming.
Not really horror?
What do you mean?
That game was fucking terrifying.
Soma was really scary for me.
Man, I jumped and screamed a lot when I played that.
But I'm also very jumpy, so...
Oh man, that game is so good.
The writing and the story in that one is incredible.
Oh, I'm done with the stream now, Luca.
I'm not going to play anymore today.
But thanks for stopping by.
I've not played Mortuary Assistant.
Unless you're asking if I had a job like that once.
OG Doom?
I've never played the OG one.
Anyway, I've been thinking about the tacos for a while now.
I'm going to go eat them.
And you guys have tortillas to get to, I know that.
So, thank you for watching.
I'm sorry for, uh...
You know, sucking at the game at times.
I definitely had some frustrations today at certain points, but...
I got those out of my system.
And now we're doing great progress.
And I'm actually glad that I got through that point.
Anyway, thanks for watching.
I'll see you next time.
Bye-bye.